<<<<<<< HEAD
{
  "flashcards": [
    {
      "id": "N5Y1y2kUadl6K8vSIDkom",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "Don't even",
      "back": "\"Don't even\" is a slang expression meaning \"not even\" or \"don't bother.\" It's used to warn someone not to do or say something, expressing surprise, outrage, or rejection.",
      "example": "Person 1: \"Can you lend me some money?\"\nPerson 2: \"Don't even think about it.\""
    },
    {
      "id": "tUqyn5p945dCuLRlizvzp",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "committed",
      "back": "verpflichtet",
      "example": "We are fully committed to Equal Opportunity policies."
    },
    {
      "id": "l0WWhK4q6pnIwqfRDBsmT",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "One or two differences",
      "back": "a lot ... (know a thing or two about something)",
      "example": "She knows a thing or two about international law (Sie weißt viel und ist erfahren)"
    },
    {
      "id": "wzZDlWEMdt8-QG7oPr-w1",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "To be well put toghether",
      "back": "looks good and dresses well (حواسشون به لباس پوشیدنشون هست)",
      "example": "She's elegant and well put toghether."
    },
    {
      "id": "5t38KWgl3bbDk1hDKLtK5",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "acknowledge",
      "back": "anerkennen",
      "example": "Both defendants refused to acknowledge the authority of the court.\nShe won't acknowledge that there's a problem."
    },
    {
      "id": "G1GlZKHcJnWSPUfzFOWgG",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "mean",
      "back": "gemein",
      "example": "That was a mean thing to do."
    },
    {
      "id": "C7wv4SqgtrLnX5nuxQI2e",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "tease",
      "back": "ärgern",
      "example": "She used to tease me about my hair."
    },
    {
      "id": "88V2pR3qQzb4eUFVxZBB8",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "Few nights in to s.th",
      "back": "از اول تا آخر چیزی",
      "example": "The movie was terrible. 30 minutes into it, l left the theater."
    },
    {
      "id": "QgjEFwJuLm-Dt8psn1kJQ",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "To be like",
      "back": "to say",
      "example": "I was like, \"What's the best way to learn English?\""
    },
    {
      "id": "bk7NU6sPJVjCbf59thzJ2",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "someone or s.th is somthing else",
      "back": "کسی یا چیزی استسنایی یا خاصه(er ist was anderes)",
      "example": "They're all good soccer players, but Mark is really something else."
    },
    {
      "id": "wn-zQ6WcsBgol2lITVRpU",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "four basic conditional forms?",
      "back": "",
      "example": "1.Zero Conditional: Used to express a general truth or a scientific fact.\nExample: \"If you heat ice, it melts.\"\n\n2.First Conditional: Used to express a future possibility or probability.\nExample: \"If it rains, I will stay at home.\"\n\n3.Second Conditional: Used to express an imaginary or hypothetical situation.\nExample: \"If I won the lottery, I would buy a house.\"\n\n4.Third Conditional: Used to express a hypothetical past situation and its hypothetical past result.\nExample: \"If I had studied harder, I would have passed the exam.\""
    },
    {
      "id": "2ukEDi68fCCXvshkp4QhZ",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "second or third conditionals?",
      "back": "",
      "example": "1) Second Conditional: Describes a hypothetical ***present or future*** situation and its likely outcome.\nIf she had a car, she could drive to work.\nIf I knew how to swim, I would go to the beach more often.\n\n2) Third Conditional: Describes a hypothetical ***past situation*** and its imagined result.\nIf I had gone to the party, I would have met her.\nIf I had studied harder, I would have passed the exam."
    },
    {
      "id": "pGC-qpQXgtWbQsXl8x7p0",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "Mixed conditionals?",
      "back": "",
      "example": "These types of sentences are used to talk about a situation that started in the past and has consequences in the present or future.Here are a few examples of mixed conditionals:If she had listened to the advice, she wouldn't be in this situation now. (third conditional + second conditional)If I had known about the traffic, I would be at work now. (third conditional + present simple)If he had taken his umbrella, he wouldn't be wet now. (third conditional + present continuous)"
    },
    {
      "id": "f_KXya7icYTuTABXToQQl",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Umgangsprachliche \"This is going to get you\"",
      "back": "this is gonna getch-ya",
      "example": "\"This is going to get you\" bedeutet in der Regel, dass etwas negative Auswirkungen auf jemanden haben wird oder dass jemand in Schwierigkeiten geraten wird."
    },
    {
      "id": "Ok6pP_rqMVNMT_JzfIUU0",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "out there",
      "back": "anywhere outside",
      "example": "\"There are so many opportunities waiting for us out there, we just need to be brave enough to go after them.\""
    },
    {
      "id": "Tu4foX5gRWQ_kYxzAiao9",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Umgangssprachliche \"Had you ...\"",
      "back": "ha-ju ....",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "iREP1fy1Wu6l4G4lx1ouc",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "attorney",
      "back": "Rechtsanwalt",
      "example": "\"My attorney advised me to take the plea deal to avoid a lengthy court battle.\""
    },
    {
      "id": "ZjGbN6VlHPi16SywiY5Fy",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "would (andere Bedeutung)",
      "back": "a routine action in the past",
      "example": "When I was a kid my grandma always would tell me to eat all my vegetables."
    },
    {
      "id": "XXvBxXiAqGDFOadz8hRsF",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "Get into trouble",
      "back": "Schwierigkeiten bekommem oder in Schwierigkeiten geraten",
      "example": "he got into trouble with the police."
    },
    {
      "id": "wkWqPQfq-mblbWslDb1U1",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "white picket fence",
      "back": "The american Dream (a strong symbol)",
      "example": "Der Begriff wird oft verwendet, um das Konzept einer perfekten, friedlichen und sicheren Umgebung zu beschreiben"
    },
    {
      "id": "Pw8bYhfIjIwda2ei-GOYc",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "Doing what i'm doing",
      "back": "dass man an seiner gegenwärtigen Arbeit, seinem Projekt oder seiner Verpflichtung festhält und weitermacht.",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "C9QtLoXScG0uLGHfvXvbE",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "Good old (ol')",
      "back": "for something reliable (vertraut)",
      "example": "All I need to feel happy is my favorite music and this good ol' journal"
    },
    {
      "id": "jB9rdO5O25zfd9y29xQEB",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "A lot of times (sound?)",
      "back": "a-lodda times",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "X0oqvddu7Yw0DZCNZqTQL",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "Get on well with someone",
      "back": "get along with someone(American)",
      "example": "I get on well with my mother-in-law"
    },
    {
      "id": "1wQJYF2V3p3v7KecINxwv",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "Down-to-earth",
      "back": "bodenständig",
      "example": "Fran’s a friendly, down-to-earth person."
    },
    {
      "id": "Uf385Iysk-SM_KitG2mSv",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "Stick together",
      "back": "if people stick together, they continue to support each other when they have problems (zusammenhalten)",
      "example": "We’re a family, and we stick together no matter what."
    },
    {
      "id": "UrR7BZgtcWSuJkXZK4UJX",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Hurl",
      "back": "to throw something with a lot of force, especially because you are angry",
      "example": "They hurled a rock through the window"
    },
    {
      "id": "UTNWkSSBsqO95-2j-umPS",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Plummet",
      "back": "abstürzen",
      "example": "The plane plummeted towards the Earth."
    },
    {
      "id": "L9Hwv-DslYjoI7--aMjQW",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "chute (شوت)",
      "back": "short for parachute",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "tYW-8zIFiXbh-tnLSWu-M",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Eight by ten glossies (گلاسیس) of my life",
      "back": "اون حالتی که قبل مرگ تمام خاطرات جلوی چشم آدم میاد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "16KBwX708F0WZ0y17zQAi",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Why do I have to die today (sound?)",
      "back": "why do i hafta die du-day",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "6ScietzgEOLw0gsvKYEgQ",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "nasal breathing",
      "back": "Nasenatmung",
      "example": "Nasal breathing helps to keep the mouth closed, which can improve overall breathing."
    },
    {
      "id": "p5mnrewVMD7yA3qDxevy3",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "Flossing ",
      "back": "Zahnseide, Zahnseide benutzen",
      "example": "Flossing has several advantages for oral health"
    },
    {
      "id": "bWZvmSC47RdlN-6nTRfYj",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "to come in late ",
      "back": " to arrive at a place after the expected or scheduled time",
      "example": "I'm afraid I'll come in late to the meeting today"
    },
    {
      "id": "v9bK9K44q54zU5lPwht4O",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "Raving about something",
      "back": "to express strong and enthusiastic praise or admiration for something",
      "example": "I was raving about the new restaurant I tried last night"
    },
    {
      "id": "0Ez9Np9pKetON_JPOo9Mv",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "To binge-watch",
      "back": "to watch multiple episodes of a television show or multiple movies in a single sitting, often in one day or over a short period of time.",
      "example": "I've been binge-watching the season since this morning."
    },
    {
      "id": "y4UG1YDCOSwLxX6vm8X6s",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "Ahead of time",
      "back": "means before the scheduled or expected time",
      "example": "I finished my work ahead of time"
    },
    {
      "id": "bUWjIKTGmgqZZUuKWdMje",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "This is going to be huge",
      "back": "it is going to become very popular or famous",
      "example": "I think this band is going to be huge."
    },
    {
      "id": "gPCBukZrbXXqY2RPc_Cmj",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "one of those things",
      "back": " is used to describe something that is difficult to explain or understand, or something that is unpredictable or beyond control",
      "example": "It's just one of those things, there's not much we can do about it"
    },
    {
      "id": "jDL7936KusaRnh7TrUyd_",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "to make it",
      "back": " means to succeed or to achieve something, especially in a difficult or competitive situation",
      "example": "We need to make it to the top of the mountain if we want to see the view"
    },
    {
      "id": "_aO3VAvD2roVyvEyj1d27",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "Duvet",
      "back": "لحاف",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "zn6TKxU6-rb08izTdbhlo",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "sheet",
      "back": "ملافه",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "p1igMoSZ-xifcj9fMcqY2",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "to yank",
      "back": "to pull or tug something suddenly and with force",
      "example": "He yanked her to her feet"
    },
    {
      "id": "RINSjK7FBu6ZfmEHZqofa",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "Tasefully done",
      "back": "that something has been done in a way that is pleasing to the senses or in good taste",
      "example": "I usually find tattoss ugly, but i like hers. It is small and tasteful."
    },
    {
      "id": "NDAGAV4ycd0GS_PLRo6bD",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "it drives me crazy wenn...",
      "back": "es macht mich wahnsinnig wenn... دیوانه ام می کند",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "7JoHo7x5HKWcUMJ3P6JPH",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "wish + past simple",
      "back": "is used to express that we want a situation in the present (or future) to be different.",
      "example": "I wish I spoke Italian. (I don’t speak Italian)\nI wish I had a big car. (I don’t have a big car)\nI wish I were on a beach. (I’m in the office)\nI wish it were the weekend. (It’s only Wednesday)"
    },
    {
      "id": "Zz-vjhY1fo9jexdsdvNeb",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "Wish + would / wouldn't",
      "back": "wish + would + bare infinitive is used to express impatience, annoyance or dissatisfaction with a present action.",
      "example": "I wish you would stop smoking.\nYou are smoking at the moment and it is annoying me.\n\nI wish it would stop raining.\nI’m impatient because it is raining and I want to go outside.\n\nI wish she’d be quiet.\nI am annoyed because she is speaking."
    },
    {
      "id": "5mcDcaHADB4rUddcKbQIP",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "wish + past perfect",
      "back": "is used to express a regret, or that we want a situation in the past to be different.",
      "example": "I wish I hadn’t eaten so much. (I ate a lot)\nI wish they’d come on holiday with us. (They didn’t come on holiday)\nI wish I had studied harder at school. (I was lazy at school)"
    },
    {
      "id": "8FcmEmiDolIuHvzYx5uLu",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "if only",
      "back": "used instead of \"i wish\" to express deep regret",
      "example": "If only I had paid more attention in class, I would have understood the material better. (The speaker expresses regret about not paying enough attention in a past class, wishing they had understood the material better.)"
    },
    {
      "id": "btZpfbxrzX5QD-Bl1xI-_",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "blush",
      "back": "erröten,  to become red in the face, usually because you are embarrassed",
      "example": "Wilson saw she was watching him and blushed."
    },
    {
      "id": "_aESdt9nIqbgZ7CARHgEC",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "dumb",
      "back": " informal stupid",
      "example": "What a dumb question."
    },
    {
      "id": "Va0JZ_7WHk03olGcQzrls",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "urge ",
      "back": "a strong wish or need SYN desire",
      "example": "He could no longer resist the urge to go and see Amanda."
    },
    {
      "id": "1pqc-TIpJtjWrMZh9A7st",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "kneel",
      "back": "زانو زدن",
      "example": "Tom knelt down and patted the dog."
    },
    {
      "id": "-E0-6ZYQnBsFCAUTuyU3M",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "Do you get that from people?",
      "back": "Do people tell you that? مردم زیاد بهت میگن؟",
      "example": "A:Man, you really look like Chandler from Friends.\nB: I get that a lot."
    },
    {
      "id": "DuLhKg-uwwBSjLJvP0mh7",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "what's up? meaning and sound?",
      "back": "was geht? (wassup), چه خبر",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "aS9588u4yIIa13ytGqgvo",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "from afar",
      "back": "از دور",
      "example": "I saw him from afar."
    },
    {
      "id": "Aj6VU16WPygxuk98OTawb",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "nuts /nʌts/",
      "back": " informal  crazy",
      "example": "I’m going to go nuts (=become crazy) if I don’t find a new job soon."
    },
    {
      "id": "GztdlSQext74AfS4LAsQB",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "be nuts about/over somebody/something",
      "back": " informal to like someone or something very much",
      "example": "My wife is nuts about kids."
    },
    {
      "id": "Af5K6Lrq5C0tfYSquckXf",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "mud /mʌd/",
      "back": "گل و لای",
      "example": "By the end of the game, all the kids were covered in mud."
    },
    {
      "id": "0gKyp582Jk4-FKK3Vy2lk",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "harrowing ˈhærəʊɪŋ ",
      "back": "very frightening or shocking and making you feel very upset. qualvoll",
      "example": "a harrowing experience"
    },
    {
      "id": "E1_1_aSAvOSh8VToRxVAf",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "warehouse",
      "back": "انبار",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "3kdFGmy7vrHShRtJO5B1R",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "contraption kənˈtræpʃən",
      "back": "a piece of equipment or machinery that looks funny, strange, and unlikely to work well",
      "example": "a bizarre contraption"
    },
    {
      "id": "dBM6W-roAWvOVQMIczh1c",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "go haywire ˈheɪwaɪə ",
      "back": "informal to start working in completely the wrong way",
      "example": "My computer’s gone haywire"
    },
    {
      "id": "WEynDla4oSp-cD6E3l0pn",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "make a point of doing something",
      "back": "bedeutet, dass man sich bewusst Zeit nimmt und Anstrengungen unternimmt, um etwas zu tun, das man für wichtig hält.",
      "example": "I always make a point of being early."
    },
    {
      "id": "PDvThGjF68TPk2kqpdmRR",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "big deal",
      "back": "an important or exciting event or situation",
      "example": "This audition is a big deal for Joey."
    },
    {
      "id": "eqZzDXuk_WH2X1Beg_2Lt",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "no big deal",
      "back": "used to say that you do not think something is as important as someone else thinks it is",
      "example": "It’s no big deal. Everybody forgets things sometimes"
    },
    {
      "id": "dDMEW5N-sOBMcec8_NSO8",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "testicle  ˈtestɪkəl",
      "back": "Hoden, خایه",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "vFqXOpVTEsFxtSNTc6jpb",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "it pains somebody to do something",
      "back": "formal used to say that it is very difficult and upsetting for someone to have to do something",
      "example": "Most burglars, it pains me to say, are just looking for the easy dollar."
    },
    {
      "id": "veNKgk5WVrAjMaTHdLZLr",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "to mess with someone",
      "back": "sich mit jemandem anlegen",
      "example": "I've warned you already, don't mess with me!"
    },
    {
      "id": "EG8EpS8Y0s2xHfpedH4IK",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "endeavor ɪnˈdevə ",
      "back": "formal to try very hard",
      "example": "We always endeavor to please our customers."
    },
    {
      "id": "t7gMK_0480lqPZCzAvOl5",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "voluntarily",
      "back": "freiwillig, به طور داوطلبانه",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "gJqsRsCNW5aNQuoVHj257",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "kind of (sound)",
      "back": "kina کاینا",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "UAEgYzV7FzqIGQYyiPhRL",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "mess up phrasal verb informal",
      "back": "to make a mistake and do something badly",
      "example": "I think I messed up on the last question."
    },
    {
      "id": "S0SvH5UXgBl5N3jkodOmw",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "shot ",
      "back": "informal an attempt to do something or achieve something, especially something difficult",
      "example": "I didn’t think I had much chance of winning the race, but I thought I’d give it a shot (=try to do it)."
    },
    {
      "id": "ZjdHwU1O_cIHAv9Naqjla",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "to blow",
      "back": "informal to lose a good opportunity by making a mistake or by being careless",
      "example": "You’ve got a great future ahead of you. Don’t blow it."
    },
    {
      "id": "W8c4zyQ52qTepjCmM_f1K",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "be meant for somebody",
      "back": "if two people are meant for each other, they are very suitable as partners for each other",
      "example": "They were meant for each other(Sie waren füreinander bestimmt.)."
    },
    {
      "id": "FcVkNYumwf3rcpptOPtQ3",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "mental ˈmentl",
      "back": "British English informal thinking or behaving in a way that seems crazy or strange",
      "example": "He must be mental!(Er muss verrückt sein!)"
    },
    {
      "id": "6qkRZ7CP7tgkEDk6q01ZW",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "wig ",
      "back": "Perücke",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "1NjRnOn2px_72LxSiodVA",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "itchy ˈɪtʃi",
      "back": "خارش‌دار , juckend",
      "example": "My eyes sometimes get red and itchy in the summer."
    },
    {
      "id": "sEg2yNdxkAZm9abtm2pNQ",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "sue",
      "back": "verklagen",
      "example": "If the builders don’t fulfil their side of the contract, we’ll sue."
    },
    {
      "id": "Q8Y-fYinb_Drj9JHSwniN",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "flick through",
      "back": "Durchblättern",
      "example": "Will flicked through Carla’s photo album."
    },
    {
      "id": "4Kr84G0A0qHOl4Ih8FGZi",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "make it",
      "back": " informal to continue to live after you have been seriously ill or badly injured",
      "example": "Frank was very ill, and the doctors didn’t think he’d make it"
    },
    {
      "id": "5jBXXrJdGhzWKzF6o5M1X",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "screw around",
      "back": "informal to do silly things that may cause trouble SYN mess around",
      "example": "The kids were screwing around down by the bus station."
    },
    {
      "id": "d-z5v2PrjI8i3Hls1QCkS",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "culprit  ˈkʌlprɪt",
      "back": "مقصر",
      "example": "Police finally managed to catch the culprit."
    },
    {
      "id": "cY_Lxd1GBUVRw8CA06rvt",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "root for somebody",
      "back": "informal to want someone to succeed in a competition, test, or difficult situation",
      "example": "You can do it – I’m rooting for you"
    },
    {
      "id": "FbdQ8iwLiYhvfSKtqXyWj",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "knackered ˈnækəd ",
      "back": "adjective British English spoken informal  too old or broken to use",
      "example": "a knackered old bike"
    },
    {
      "id": "f1yiuhAJuWCTS1YB0qFCg",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "how did that go?",
      "back": "Wie ging das?  چطور شد؟",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "ykfPRjoBRiiu_dTJPEdmp",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "so that in essence",
      "back": "also im Wesentlichen",
      "example": "I condensed my report to only include the key findings so that in essence, the reader can quickly grasp the main points."
    },
    {
      "id": "1KYctKQytFewXzqCi_FFY",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "on the flip side",
      "back": "bedeutet, dass man eine andere Perspektive oder Sichtweise betrachtet. Es wird verwendet, um einen Gegensatz oder eine Alternative zu einer bereits vorgestellten Idee oder Argumentation darzustellen. ",
      "example": "On the flip side, while the new policy may be beneficial in some ways, it could also result in unintended consequences that need to be considered."
    },
    {
      "id": "A7tEVdZRyi98EuSkrSCjx",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "that is freaking awesome",
      "back": "das ist wahnsinnig toll",
      "example": "The new virtual reality game is so realistic and immersive, that is freaking awesome!"
    },
    {
      "id": "URXAhevH84TBcAbussPX0",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "revert to",
      "back": " zurückzukehren oder zurückzugreifen auf etwas, das man früher hatte oder tat.",
      "example": "Due to technical difficulties, we had to revert to the manual process for the time being until the system is fixed."
    },
    {
      "id": "6jjSi-VWblyLrWMQkZGJK",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "To be tricky",
      "back": "bedeutet, dass jemand schwierig, knifflig oder listig ist. Es kann bedeuten, dass eine Person absichtlich versucht, andere zu täuschen oder zu verwirren.",
      "example": "The crossword puzzle was tricky, but I finally figured out all the answers."
    },
    {
      "id": "t4QfdNcWZDaxNv7lbvhem",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "no fucking way",
      "back": "auf keinen Fall",
      "example": "I heard that the company is planning to lay off half the staff, and I'm telling you, there's no fucking way that's going to happen without a fight"
    },
    {
      "id": "tnkDDD8t8xI2HmP_r5dSx",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "To sleep over",
      "back": "to sleep at another person's house",
      "example": "I slept over at my friend's house."
    },
    {
      "id": "p9oYZDnFclJB0AgSVMSGu",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "to go for a wee",
      "back": "is a colloquial expression used to describe someone going to urinate.",
      "example": "he went for a wee."
    },
    {
      "id": "DpRiE2X5KBoUC7WliptYU",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "favorite curse word",
      "back": "Lieblingsschimpfwort",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "hVn3MiITbMU3ANIRfwZWk",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "go out on a limb",
      "back": "The expression is often used to describe a situation where someone takes a bold or unpopular stance, or makes a bold or risky decision.",
      "example": "John decided to go out on a limb and start his own business, even though he knew it would be a big risk."
    },
    {
      "id": "VOicgMd7esVcuC56pPazI",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "What is your (sound)",
      "back": "waddiz-yir ",
      "example": "waddiz-yir favorite body part?"
    },
    {
      "id": "TIkskiYvUPro933YnASC-",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "though",
      "back": "spoken used after adding a fact, opinion, or question which seems surprising after what you have just said, or which makes what you have just said seem less true",
      "example": "Two heart attacks in a year. It hasn’t stopped him smoking, though."
    },
    {
      "id": "QGJMAvhQmVBIfMVuC2Mr4",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "perform a task",
      "back": "انجام یک وظیفه یا کاری",
      "example": "the surgeon performed the operation without complications."
    },
    {
      "id": "kR9FG7UzTMzpu7wFjbBtw",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "to curse",
      "back": "schimpfen",
      "example": "Don't curse in front of the kids!"
    },
    {
      "id": "XIBhmNYkiZlxU527de96S",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "impersonate",
      "back": "imitieren,  to pretend to be someone else by copying their appearance, voice, and behaviour, especially in order to deceive people",
      "example": "Do you know it is a very serious offence to impersonate a police officer?"
    },
    {
      "id": "oFmnbqCB9MmJMcPulIohu",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "Yell at",
      "back": "فریاد زدن برسر, Anschreien",
      "example": "He yelled \"Watch out!\""
    },
    {
      "id": "JQkJuQpZ3KPyF5CCPie-t",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "cool-headed",
      "back": "not easily excited or upset, خونسرد",
      "example": "We need a quick-thinking, cool-headed person for the job."
    },
    {
      "id": "AsmEL_FGopmR1G9JqfBZn",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "hothead",
      "back": "someone who does things too quickly without thinking",
      "example": "neither of you hotheads would listen to me when I asked you to stop this nonsense"
    },
    {
      "id": "gC-acuU0Zhj_Wkd0pX56P",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "call somebody/something ↔ off",
      "back": "to decide that a planned event will not take place SYN cancel",
      "example": "The trip to Italy might be called off."
    },
    {
      "id": "IRS_jVzBMPAh2ECKo_rZV",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "go astray",
      "back": "to be lost or stolen",
      "example": "The letter had gone astray in the post."
    },
    {
      "id": "5qXrBR6CDwIbVgyeu5FSp",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "airship",
      "back": "بالون",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "tRI1-176mYnNpUwwZ-6R0",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "debris  ˈdebriː",
      "back": "باقی مانده, خرده",
      "example": "the bomb hits it, showering debris from all sides"
    },
    {
      "id": "ABSbyrAGZxTiRBYLRYhnB",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "fray",
      "back": "increasingly upset or annoying",
      "example": "amid fraying tensions"
    },
    {
      "id": "wFtnfIejRyUzRnkhj1Noj",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "violate  ˈvaɪəleɪt",
      "back": "verletzen, نقض کردن",
      "example": "regimes that violate human rights"
    },
    {
      "id": "xwDdX04vCihEu0aD3eABX",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "territory",
      "back": "Staatsgebiet",
      "example": "The plane was flying over enemy territory."
    },
    {
      "id": "euUNY5faUTDONUXcClsdS",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "sovereign country",
      "back": "کشور مستقل",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "RyLUT2jReWCREzhQZxE1e",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "in a calm and reliable manner",
      "back": "به شیوه ای آرام و قابل اعتماد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "GNKMZ_fXPWLmjdJ03Z8Aq",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "would not accept any groundless conjecture or hype",
      "back": "هیچ گونه حدس و گمان یا هیاهوی بی اساس را نمی پذیرد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "9zUpPJsdvkciOiNH096Zn",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "as a pretext to attack and smear China",
      "back": "بهانه ای برای حمله و لکه دار کردن چین است",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "7xU9toIib5Xh30s_CpVuP",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "US officials",
      "back": "مقامات آمریکایی",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "gwdv2hm7PcR2cMsvpw4Fd",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "missile",
      "back": "موشک",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "0k-fw1oHZ77Dtd_WWItlw",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "the eve of",
      "back": "the night before",
      "example": "I'm planning a nice dinner the eve of my wedding. "
    },
    {
      "id": "kJPEEZfGECpU-GmJDd1an",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "to show up",
      "back": "to arrive",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "K8Ww8LtyzBd3iP_EgBlBT",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "stuck",
      "back": "informal unable to do any more of something that you are working on because it is too difficult",
      "example": "Can you help me with my homework, Dad? I’m stuck."
    },
    {
      "id": "SUa0v1fD33WchMt9hGvDN",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "anticipate   /ænˈtɪsəpeɪt/",
      "back": " to think about something that is going to happen, especially something pleasant SYN look forward to (erwarten)",
      "example": "Daniel was eagerly anticipating her arrival."
    },
    {
      "id": "M-kbntGRtZIFoGgG8NlWL",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "make it to some place",
      "back": "arrive",
      "example": "I can't believe I made it to the job interview in time. I was stuck in traffic for 20 minutes."
    },
    {
      "id": "gO9DXXka4FQOh66CvkC-s",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "tie تای",
      "back": "مساوی ",
      "example": "Who won the game?\nNobody. It was a tie (game/match)."
    },
    {
      "id": "5uDOruGua_rWwwMZZfAfA",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "opt for / opt to do something",
      "back": "to choose one thing or do one thing instead of another, انتخاب کردن",
      "example": "Many young people are opting to go on to college."
    },
    {
      "id": "XS3PpytrDNWNJy0L3IYKX",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "My hair is down",
      "back": "Meine Haare sind offen",
      "example": "opp: My hair is up"
    },
    {
      "id": "mB7VUOxs2dvbTfFwRr3cg",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "wonky /ˈwɒŋki",
      "back": "wackelig",
      "example": "i was wonky"
    },
    {
      "id": "Lcr2heuG3V9oBU8keS9B-",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": " out of sorts",
      "back": "feeling a little ill or upset ",
      "example": "I felt out of sorts after riding in the boat."
    },
    {
      "id": "WrKXRuTXk2cmpQnhMVCcE",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "tummy",
      "back": "Magen",
      "example": "He was up all night with tummy ache."
    },
    {
      "id": "f8DXSU17TXf5hpyNCFUvs",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "for real",
      "back": "wirklich, seriously, not just pretending",
      "example": "After two trial runs we did it for real."
    },
    {
      "id": "PADuK4hYKcSVdJMiBQdoa",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "with my luck...",
      "back": "Pech!, Wie immer!, spoken used to say that you are not surprised something bad has happened to you, because you are usually unlucky",
      "example": "With my luck, gambling is a really bad idea."
    },
    {
      "id": "okXaxFsEeST3H418f4rAM",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "bottoms up!",
      "back": "spoken used to tell someone to enjoy or finish their alcoholic drink",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "VfCSwLyM8Y0_PPDjUEkeJ",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "smooth sailing",
      "back": "happening or operating successfully, without any problems",
      "example": "Sarah is responsible for the smooth sailing of the sales department."
    },
    {
      "id": "X2AYoccU5nrgLTY-tcX39",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "Bottoms up (sound?)",
      "back": "ba-dum-zup  بدمز آپ",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "ZIHrrEGjHGxY5i2HJ9ijI",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "sort of thing",
      "back": "Dass etwas typisch ist",
      "example": "Eating peanuts is a very baseball game sort of thing."
    },
    {
      "id": "_uExncVT9bn_SlOx04_f4",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "he hit on me",
      "back": "\"Er hat versucht, mich anzumachen\". Das bedeutet, dass jemand versucht hat, romantische oder sexuelle Aufmerksamkeit von Ihnen zu bekommen.",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "EE61JTtBwFlsazqBS8wdz",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "Break down",
      "back": "Zusammenbrechen, fehlschlagen, ausfallen",
      "example": "The car broke down on the highway."
    },
    {
      "id": "48ZxwKKxCwG42eOSuReF5",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "Call off",
      "back": "Absagen, abbrechen",
      "example": "We had to call off the party due to bad weather."
    },
    {
      "id": "dwQwvtBQ6-HEX9D0sB4GL",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "Come up with",
      "back": "Etwas erfinden, sich etwas ausdenken",
      "example": "I need to come up with a good excuse for being late."
    },
    {
      "id": "NoaXJ6W0-2TlZn2zjpap1",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Put off",
      "back": "Verschieben, aufschieben",
      "example": "I keep putting off doing my taxes."
    },
    {
      "id": "tf5m0FOCX1odGipKFTKrf",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Turn down",
      "back": "Ablehnen, abweisen",
      "example": "I applied for the job, but they turned me down."
    },
    {
      "id": "qgC5781pbSo6n1ww8gbDT",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "Work out",
      "back": "Sich herausstellen, funktionieren, trainieren",
      "example": "I hope everything works out in the end."
    },
    {
      "id": "pHC8GId428Jrt-xgr8SGT",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Bring up",
      "back": "Jemanden auf etwas ansprechen, aufziehen (Kinder)",
      "example": "I don't want to bring up that topic again."
    },
    {
      "id": "2DwkGmMpvIz3JLhaVelE_",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "Put up with",
      "back": " Etwas ertragen, sich mit etwas abfinden",
      "example": "I can't put up with his behavior anymore."
    },
    {
      "id": "2FXfgqt1xfW2KXaDgDkVQ",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Turn up",
      "back": "Auftauchen, erscheinen, erhöhen",
      "example": "He turned up at the party unexpectedly."
    },
    {
      "id": "GtMxMSnj-D9y9XKCLXTSX",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Get away",
      "back": "Wegkommen, fliehen, eine Pause machen",
      "example": "I need to get away from work for a few days."
    },
    {
      "id": "j9Tw5zLmK1rN8sQ2fYxuq",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "procrastinate",
      "back": "aufschieben",
      "example": "I tend to procrastinate when I have a lot of work to do."
    },
    {
      "id": "s7Tk2hPnL8qF3mJ6dYxrz",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "reliable",
      "back": "zuverlässig",
      "example": "He is a reliable worker who always gets the job done on time."
    },
    {
      "id": "t9X2f8kYj1rL7sG6mDxuq",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "vulnerable",
      "back": "verletzlich",
      "example": "She felt vulnerable after the breakup."
    },
    {
      "id": "f9T2z1hKj1eL7sG6mDxuq",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "resilient",
      "back": "widerstandsfähig",
      "example": "She is a resilient person who can handle tough situations."
    },
    {
      "id": "g9T2z1hKj1rL7sD6mYxuq",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "spontaneous",
      "back": "spontan",
      "example": "She is a spontaneous person who likes to try new things."
    },
    {
      "id": "p5Ty2fKJh9eL7sG6mDxuq",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "impartial",
      "back": "unparteiisch, بی طرف",
      "example": "The judge was impartial in the case."
    },
    {
      "id": "l5Ty2pLJd1qN8sD6fYxrz",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "precise",
      "back": "präzise",
      "example": "He is very precise in his work."
    },
    {
      "id": "y9T2z1hKj1eL7sG6mDxuq",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "versatile",
      "back": "vielseitig",
      "example": "She is a versatile performer who can sing, dance, and act."
    },
    {
      "id": "a5Ty2pLJd1qN8sQ6fYxrz",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "conscientious",
      "back": "gewissenhaft, با وجدان",
      "example": "She is a conscientious worker who always pays attention to details."
    },
    {
      "id": "2udHLlU0SIazVUwrk6XyA",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Clunky and verbose",
      "back": "bedeutet, dass etwas schwerfällig und umständlich ist und dabei unnötig viele Worte verwendet werden.",
      "example": "The program's documentation was clunky and verbose, spanning hundreds of pages even though most of the information could have been summarized in just a few."
    },
    {
      "id": "x9CdOfnLs-moT2ho-bt6L",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "schema",
      "back": "طرح , das Schema, die Darstellung",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "dvqcHPoasy3I2ZNGE5Zix",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "for the sake of this tutorial",
      "back": "به خاطر این آموزش",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "TgzYEp2Y_nfEX0qpR76mP",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "you're bound to get replaced",
      "back": "شما محکوم به جایگزینی هستید",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "UrQQlHGl3VQEKzg-e7Jkb",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "in response to",
      "back": "als Antwort auf",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "bIP-yYLHc6xDNcO95juJM",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "blog snippet",
      "back": "قطعه وبلاگ, Blogausschnitt",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "ttj1VR5p_ZrlWU-VzwCjO",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "in the face of something",
      "back": "angesichts von etwas, با وجود ",
      "example": "In the face of adversity, she remained steadfast and focused on her goals."
    },
    {
      "id": "hQ7jx7SHEDGuzZXcqMUBo",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "to be eligible",
      "back": "anspruchsberechtigt sein, berechtigt sein zu, واجد شرایط بودن",
      "example": "In order to be eligible for the scholarship, applicants must have a minimum GPA of 3.5."
    },
    {
      "id": "1EnC0Z-g0zb0PRq1LTIL1",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "infuriate  ɪnˈfjʊərieɪt ",
      "back": "to make someone extremely angry SYN anger",
      "example": "It infuriated him that Beth was with another man."
    },
    {
      "id": "nfoyrMvzMg8OLfU8XPFEB",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "offensive   əˈfensɪv",
      "back": "very rude or insulting and likely to upset people OPP inoffensive",
      "example": "I found her remarks deeply offensive."
    },
    {
      "id": "PkwQpOtHHTNGhbcaRn2ui",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "freshman year dorm room",
      "back": "اتاق خواب سال اول, Studentenwohnheim im ersten Jahr",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "zWZXnQ7LJKuNVHTWGpYgj",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "devastatingly",
      "back": " to an extremely impressive degree.",
      "example": "a devastatingly attractive man"
    },
    {
      "id": "QXVmjD4M18TXk0WBiC-KX",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "sorrow  ˈsɒrəʊ ",
      "back": "Kummer, Leid , غم و اندوه",
      "example": "He expressed his sorrow at my father’s death."
    },
    {
      "id": "o7B9HHs8dV_s5tcdbGS5E",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "encouraging",
      "back": "viel versprechend, دلگرم کننده",
      "example": "The signs are encouraging — but there’s a long way to go."
    },
    {
      "id": "sdgnNBsQeUHvS48XO68Q6",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "alongside",
      "back": "در کنار",
      "example": "Children’s prices are shown alongside adult prices."
    },
    {
      "id": "FmyVWDK9PhBT80eZT9m6v",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "intriguing     ɪnˈtriːɡɪŋ",
      "back": "جذاب , faszinierend",
      "example": "The magazine carries an intriguing mixture of high fashion, gossip and racing."
    },
    {
      "id": "MMBuRhVhMvWZzPa_P9t8X",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "brave",
      "back": "شجاع",
      "example": "a brave soldier"
    },
    {
      "id": "vcIS1J6LsIuHL08CyVQeG",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "I'm absolutely sure we would have gotten along",
      "back": "من کاملا مطمئن هستم که با هم کنار می آمدیم",
      "example": "Ich bin mir absolut sicher, dass wir uns verstanden hätten"
    },
    {
      "id": "49ACGOvLy7lHcpxYW6z8v",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "eager  ˈiːɡə ",
      "back": "very keen and excited about something that is going to happen or about something you want to do, مشتاق",
      "example": "I was eager to get back to work as soon as possible."
    },
    {
      "id": "wBfDPZpKaS5LQBcWPbPLw",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "eager to please",
      "back": "eifrig zu gefallen,  مشتاق خوشحال کردن دیگران",
      "example": "She’s a very hard worker and very eager to please."
    },
    {
      "id": "HAyMZT-y-vjvLiUayKh3T",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": " every now and then/again",
      "back": "(also every so often) sometimes, but not often or regularly. hin und wieder, هرازگاهی/دوباره",
      "example": "I still see her every now and then."
    },
    {
      "id": "Z9pfdRmSgC_9TAgm0DUbd",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "if it's of any help",
      "back": "falls es was hilft, اگر کمکی باشد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "_gvIGfolxPkDZWp3b5dBc",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "One hell of a high five",
      "back": "",
      "example": "dass die gegebene High Five (Hand abklatschen) besonders beeindruckend oder außergewöhnlich gut war. Es kann verwendet werden, um jemanden für eine besonders gute Leistung oder eine großartige Leistung zu loben."
    },
    {
      "id": "AueKSeOtiwq2BrsMvfj-x",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "foreshadow  fɔːˈʃædəʊ ",
      "back": "to show or say that something will happen in the future, vorausahnen lassen,پیش بینی ",
      "example": "The revolution foreshadowed an entirely new social order."
    },
    {
      "id": "2rpikmo9nVSavJQeFUp-H",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "wink",
      "back": "چشمک",
      "example": "he winked at Nicole as he passed"
    },
    {
      "id": "VDkeGsdBx42ImEcz2LMUs",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": " spot-on",
      "back": "informal exactly right",
      "example": "Judith is always spot-on with her advice."
    },
    {
      "id": "A4krYJapYecUb3p4ShjJ4",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "To be off",
      "back": "not be close to right.",
      "example": "How far off have they been?"
    },
    {
      "id": "shFhsxz21Vw0O6v94tipH",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "I would have loved to (sound)",
      "back": "I would-a loved to",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "RLU_iqZrvKJuMh22kjN4a",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "let somebody/something ↔ down",
      "back": "to not do something that someone trusts or expects you to do. کسی را ناامید کن",
      "example": "The worst feeling is having let our fans down."
    },
    {
      "id": "ThTxA6RNKR1kSHvWKR_F2",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "butcher",
      "back": " informal to spoil something by working carelessly",
      "example": "That hairdresser really butchered my hair!"
    },
    {
      "id": "wRb8Orn3a5YdxLVtIOiE8",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "You're putting me on the spot",
      "back": "bedeutet, dass man unter Druck gesetzt wird, eine schnelle Entscheidung oder Antwort auf eine Frage oder Situation zu geben, für die man nicht ausreichend vorbereitet ist oder keine klare Antwort hat. Es kann auch bedeuten, dass man sich unwohl oder unsicher fühlt, wenn man in dieser Weise herausgefordert wird.",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "OlU7qC-I268hsJugrScSV",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "rummage  ˈrʌmɪdʒ",
      "back": "(also rummage around/about) to search for something by moving things around in a careless or hurried way. زیر و رو کردن",
      "example": "Looks like someone’s been rummaging around in my desk."
    },
    {
      "id": "adMyYjqhXUmj4g_HJynvC",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "Dumpster  ˈdʌmpstə ",
      "back": "Müllcontainer",
      "example": "There was a Dumpster on the street."
    },
    {
      "id": "W0z99YF6FxNFOHLCVnGfu",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "a whole lot",
      "back": "eine ganze Menge. viel",
      "example": "We’re going to have a whole lot of problems if we don’t finish this by tomorrow."
    },
    {
      "id": "PK3r-5z8d8LEqkgGdk1E7",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "you've got an issue (sound)",
      "back": "you've gah-din issue",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "siBPq0OHeOMAHf1pxev9E",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "intimacy",
      "back": "رابطه نامشروع جنسی. formal sex – used especially by lawyers and police when they want to avoid using the word ‘sex’",
      "example": "Intimacy took place on several occasions."
    },
    {
      "id": "LIfrtYNBUz1iznkDgTuQO",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "To put somebody on blast",
      "back": "bedeutet, jemanden öffentlich zu kritisieren oder bloßzustellen, oft durch die Verbreitung von Informationen oder Meinungen über diese Person in der Öffentlichkeit oder auf sozialen Medien. Es kann auch bedeuten, jemanden öffentlich zu beschuldigen oder anzugreifen. Der Ausdruck wird oft im Zusammenhang mit einer heftigen Kritik oder einer Kontroverse verwendet.",
      "example": "She put him on blast for cheating on her."
    },
    {
      "id": "rMo2R5hsgKpMCCvtAepEd",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "to hold on to somebody",
      "back": "if someone holds on to you, they remain with you or they accompany you through a difficult time.",
      "example": "If a memory holds to you, you never forget it. "
    },
    {
      "id": "-Ds_0sKbS6h6AtrL-1eD0",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "supervisor",
      "back": "سرپرست",
      "example": "Any holidays not already booked should be cleared with your supervisor."
    },
    {
      "id": "RXIBuVHVSpMmk6laW5Peu",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "occasion",
      "back": "Gelegenheit, مناسبت",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "yq0hAhcHv6HxtNV6VbUjr",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "controversial",
      "back": "بحث برانگیز",
      "example": "Why is the Koh-i-Noor diamond so controversial?"
    },
    {
      "id": "MBkd8WDhDog6Id1hixEuH",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "that wasn't a good move on your part",
      "back": "این حرکت خوبی از طرف شما نبود",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "I5P3lBwut0BFYGjmXnWMN",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "verse",
      "back": "شعر",
      "example": "Let’s sing the last verse again"
    },
    {
      "id": "JZN4ZosbTm7gVQZ3Zykrz",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "committed environmentalist",
      "back": "engagierter Umweltschützer, محیط بان متعهد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "5rO0asqvX9l4vZUSfnOjP",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "ingest  ɪnˈdʒest",
      "back": "aufnehmen, sich nehmen, بلعیدن",
      "example": "lead will poison anyone if enough is ingested"
    },
    {
      "id": "a0JDpCjvs744B0a778IIJ",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "strangely/oddly/curiously etc enough",
      "back": "merkwürdigerweise, used to say that a fact or something that happens is strange or surprising",
      "example": "Strangely enough, I didn’t feel at all nervous when I faced the audience"
    },
    {
      "id": "ot2jW8NQ993pfY_t8wBs8",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "ancient",
      "back": "باستانی کهن",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "84jnRXcWAX0nDUWiynCVA",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "formerly",
      "back": "früher, in earlier times SYN previously",
      "example": "This elegant hotel was formerly a castle."
    },
    {
      "id": "BAvxgtKpwQMmTKQAw3F-W",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": " I think it has got hope",
      "back": "Ich denke, es hat Hoffnung gemacht",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "5PlK79wIvTs4FsHEnv-hb",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "reluctant to do something  rɪˈlʌktənt",
      "back": "unwillig, بی میل بودن",
      "example": "Maddox was reluctant to talk about it."
    },
    {
      "id": "rD7V7uyO0Runo7UJbxSON",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "fragment",
      "back": " قطعه قطعه کردن یا شدن",
      "example": "his followers fragmented into sects"
    },
    {
      "id": "oFYPkli478IeKhEMPeAj3",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "deliberately  dɪˈlɪbərətli",
      "back": "done in a way that is intended or planned به عمد",
      "example": "He deliberately upset her."
    },
    {
      "id": "78U-UrdZr7q_I8LKEvqzi",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "let/get somebody off the hook",
      "back": "was bedeutet, dass jemand von einer Verpflichtung oder Verantwortung befreit wird. to allow someone or help someone to get out of a difficult situation",
      "example": "I wasn’t prepared to let her off the hook that easily."
    },
    {
      "id": "HY6zu07M07gCP4WVVbMeE",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "multifaceted",
      "back": "چند وجهی",
      "example": "a multifaceted campaign to reduce teen pregnancy"
    },
    {
      "id": "JChxHldgNdMtrokK0LpB1",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "thrifty  ˈθrɪfti",
      "back": "using money carefully and wisely SYN economical  sparsam",
      "example": "hard-working, thrifty people"
    },
    {
      "id": "aUHH0UBuZSUsoqBZ4fEwG",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "instil confidence/fear/discipline etc into somebody",
      "back": "to teach someone to think, behave, or feel in a particular way over a period of time.  beibringen, einprägen",
      "example": "A manager’s job is to instil determination into his players"
    },
    {
      "id": "siUFKCbrdquMW65BnjMxL",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "take pride in your work/appearance etc",
      "back": "to do something very carefully and well, in a way that gives you a lot of satisfaction",
      "example": "She took great pride in her appearance.\nYou should take more pride in your work."
    },
    {
      "id": "rp5gBiK0T-Mqs2qx_s1Nt",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "perpetual  pəˈpetʃuəl ",
      "back": "continuing all the time without changing or stopping SYN continuous  ständig",
      "example": "the perpetual noise of the machines"
    },
    {
      "id": "Opx1aefTSNLxKYir9f3yS",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "bins",
      "back": "سطل زباله Mülleimer",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "B87Rzid1qOMObjZpC467M",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "underway",
      "back": "در حال انجام",
      "example": "The project is already well underway."
    },
    {
      "id": "NWDDwZ7tvjRj5-rwGrN7d",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "vaguely",
      "back": "به طور مبهم",
      "example": "he vaguely remembered talking to her once"
    },
    {
      "id": "-j447SJP7sUFTBaM55661",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "get to like/know/understand somebody/something",
      "back": "to gradually begin to like, know, or understand someone or something",
      "example": "It’ll take a while for you to get to know everyone.\nAfter a while, I got to like him."
    },
    {
      "id": "9hbxEwXKYThXo0srIC4b9",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "it makes an impression on you",
      "back": "es macht einen eindruck auf dich, روی شما تاثیر می گذارد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "odzBbQCHzNT2o0R-IWQKq",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "Glorified",
      "back": "oft verwendet wird, um eine Person, Sache oder Tätigkeit als überbewertet, aufgebauscht oder übertrieben positiv dargestellt zu beschreiben. تمجید شده ",
      "example": "I did the paperwork and was basically a glorified secretary"
    },
    {
      "id": "feoaWVb0K9I-7k2f15AIw",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "chicken out",
      "back": "informal to decide at the last moment not to do something you said you would do, because you are afraid, ",
      "example": "You’re not chickening out, are you?"
    },
    {
      "id": "pnrBwTl2p5FcjNItOaV5c",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "because he chickened out (sound)",
      "back": "cuz-ee chicken-dout",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "Le8YtXIInIu4Vu-83Hzi7",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "pile",
      "back": "Haufen",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "-cTZoqUZuETaqhqDD-umT",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "gross",
      "back": "spoken very unpleasant to look at or think about SYN disgusting",
      "example": "Ooh, gross! I hate spinach!"
    },
    {
      "id": "Cg4rt44GivE2uFr1sHbIc",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "inside of the forearm",
      "back": "داخل ساعد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "P6qRar_nq1MebrlLV-OHQ",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "Get out of here!",
      "back": "express disbelief or surprise",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "uABmmivhC4iUImrJcm2C3",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "snap",
      "back": "an exclamation of surprise",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "XMRSFnal1YfoyyL0dDGwc",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "that looks bananas",
      "back": "that is very silly or crazy",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "oTyL6RWb1-IbD9zLxLoj5",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "deprecate",
      "back": "Der Begriff deprecate bedeutet, dass etwas veraltet, nicht empfohlen oder abgelehnt ist. Zum Beispiel kann eine Funktion in einem Programm als deprecated markiert werden, wenn sie durch eine neuere oder bessere Funktion ersetzt wird",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "3bMlQqX28aRXCa4bCFclU",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "Creep",
      "back": "to move in a quiet, careful way, especially to avoid attracting attention, خزیدن",
      "example": "Johann would creep into the gallery to listen to the singers."
    },
    {
      "id": "6DGKiCL0mYLH7ExyJd1mQ",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "Stay grounded",
      "back": "to be calm, realistic and in touch with yourself",
      "example": "He stayed grounded in the midst of chaos"
    },
    {
      "id": "xwfH9K_zDfCs9j47vMzZD",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "resting face",
      "back": "Gesichtsausdruck ",
      "example": "Resting face\" auch als \"Resting Bitch Face\" (kurz RBF) bezeichnet werden, was einen Gesichtsausdruck beschreibt, der unfreundlich oder abweisend wirken kann, auch wenn die Person keine negative Absicht hat."
    },
    {
      "id": "Po3kftn_oIwnxS-RJcoxe",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "forehead",
      "back": "پیشانی",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "ILI8shn6v8hl_BQ4_coKl",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "mole",
      "back": "خال",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "vD6GZTcjUpDQLuZyP7J83",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "to cover something up",
      "back": "پوشاندن چیزی",
      "example": "The company tried to cover up the environmental damage caused by its operations by withholding information from the public and manipulating scientific studies."
    },
    {
      "id": "mtkeRVfjfb3eZ78AW5V43",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "have chemistry",
      "back": "Ausdruck, der oft verwendet wird, um eine starke emotionale oder physische Anziehungskraft zwischen zwei Personen zu beschreiben.",
      "example": "From the moment they met, there was an undeniable chemistry between them that kept them talking and laughing for hours."
    },
    {
      "id": "RTUeQrZHE399sHnyhOPqr",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "The Walk of Fame",
      "back": " ist ein berühmter Gehweg auf dem Hollywood",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "P1pJuqHM31TJZHKf9FXRW",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "beyond the realm of possibility",
      "back": "der bedeutet, dass etwas so unwahrscheinlich oder unrealistisch ist, dass es nicht einmal in Betracht gezogen werden kann.",
      "example": "It's beyond the realm of possibility that we'll be able to travel back in time and change the course of history."
    },
    {
      "id": "w8ONZiu_M-fQSXJUj8zk2",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "badass",
      "back": "that's pretty cool",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "nu1Wi01IsIFyaA8MA_huj",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "wimping out",
      "back": "der bedeutet, vor einer Herausforderung oder einer Verantwortung zurückzuschrecken und nicht mutig oder entschlossen zu handeln.",
      "example": "Instead of wimping out when faced with the challenges of starting a new business, he persevered through difficult times and eventually built a successful company."
    },
    {
      "id": "tD8nLM0jPgkUqRZQ8ZxiC",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "disarming",
      "back": "making you feel less angry or disapproving towards someone, and more friendly",
      "example": "a disarming sense of humor"
    },
    {
      "id": "hD_exEXhdSnukPRbHlytv",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "be/have a blast",
      "back": "it's extremely fun",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "c5FpkbV9FXDONJss8hLuD",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "take delight in (doing) something",
      "back": "to enjoy something very much, especially something you should not do",
      "example": "Chris takes great delight in teasing his sister."
    },
    {
      "id": "pByIVQ1oR8W3YlRpN_qg1",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "rub something ↔ in  phrasal verb informal",
      "back": "to remind someone about something they want to forget, especially because they are embarrassed about it",
      "example": "“He rubbed in his victory over me”. “She rubbed in how much money she made”."
    },
    {
      "id": "Fej13TE6y99dLcF1VpmyE",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "revelation",
      "back": "Enthüllung. a surprising fact about someone or something that was previously secret and is now made known",
      "example": "He resigned after revelations about his affair"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q3qtFXh4FQuNC7newDp5V",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "intrinsically ",
      "back": "ذاتا",
      "example": "Science is seen as intrinsically good."
    },
    {
      "id": "a8nWB3GDuUqVh2ZO6cqvs",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "withholding information",
      "back": "Informationen zurückhalten/Verschweigen, ",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "Zm6b477Hwl4lJNvGfzl0X",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "to go/get off the grid",
      "back": "\"To go off the grid\" is a phrase that means to disconnect from the public utility services and become self-sufficient, often by relying on alternative sources of energy and producing one's own food and water.",
      "example": "After years of living in the city, Sarah decided to go off the grid and build a small cabin in the woods, where she could live a simpler life without relying on modern conveniences."
    },
    {
      "id": "t4lDnZXcNacFb07RvMuyL",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "to get rid of something",
      "back": "Etwas los werden",
      "example": "I need to get rid of these old clothes that no longer fit me and are taking up space in my closet."
    },
    {
      "id": "mkwg9Zo2GH955JrQp4c6c",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "intimately",
      "back": "genau,gründlich",
      "example": "After years of marriage, Jack and Jill know each other intimately and share a strong bond."
    },
    {
      "id": "MOKkGScjKKY7SXaRua0Wj",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "to have willpower",
      "back": "Willenskraft haben",
      "example": "Despite the temptation to give in to her cravings, Sally had the willpower to stick to her diet and achieve her weight loss goals."
    },
    {
      "id": "UxmBUuaexD8UGZFjbug8t",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "to will",
      "back": "It can be used to describe something that was consciously and deliberately chosen or intended, or something that was determined by the exercise of one's willpower.",
      "example": "Despite feeling exhausted, she willed herself to keep running until she reached the finish line."
    },
    {
      "id": "fwQMR_r0QdFgK2f7DuTYg",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "cold turkey",
      "back": "The phrase \"cold turkey\" is an idiomatic expression that means to suddenly and completely stop doing something that one is addicted to, without any gradual reduction or easing of the behavior. It is often used in the context of overcoming addiction to drugs, alcohol, or tobacco.",
      "example": "After years of smoking, Jack decided to quit cold turkey and threw away all his cigarettes, even though it was a difficult and painful process."
    },
    {
      "id": "TNK4FgYQr17StUU3DI5ME",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "the point of no return",
      "back": "Der Punkt, an dem es kein Zurück mehr gibt",
      "example": "After signing the contract, we had reached the point of no return and were committed to the project, even though it was more challenging and time-consuming than we had anticipated."
    },
    {
      "id": "y8GtYwwbkwAqRfpnAfq0W",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "Figuratively",
      "back": "\"Figuratively\" is an adverb that means to use words or expressions in a non-literal way, often to create a comparison or a metaphor. It is the opposite of \"literally,\" which means to use language in its most basic and direct sense.",
      "example": "The expression \"a ray of hope\" is used figuratively to convey the idea that there is a small but significant chance of something positive happening."
    },
    {
      "id": "onG0XHvRTtfveiuFOna8s",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "threshold",
      "back": "آستانه,In figurative language, a threshold can refer to a critical point or level that marks a significant change or transition.",
      "example": "The company's profits had fallen below the threshold for several quarters, signaling the need for a change in strategy."
    },
    {
      "id": "Bb4ZcmnQ7gX0jajaPpKAt",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "Giving up a person",
      "back": "it means to end a relationship or connection with someone, either voluntarily or involuntarily.",
      "example": "After many arguments and disagreements, Mary decided to give up her boyfriend and break up with him."
    },
    {
      "id": "O7F5rOmHO6YGhpVrhElJL",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "a gig",
      "back": "A job or task, often temporary or freelance in nature, typically in the entertainment or music industry. For example, a musician might play a gig at a local bar or nightclub.",
      "example": "The band had a gig at a music festival over the weekend and played to a large and enthusiastic crowd."
    },
    {
      "id": "4S_KmhLvAVvAUiroXE17y",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "To get involved",
      "back": "درگیر شدن,means to become a participant or a part of an activity, event, or situation, often by taking an active role or showing interest in it.",
      "example": "After attending the meeting, Emily decided to get involved in the local volunteer organization and help out with their upcoming fundraiser."
    },
    {
      "id": "yKluOqDNwrgJx_OfE9cZ3",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "my bedroom window had blinds",
      "back": "پنجره اتاقم پرده داشت",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "oi7QcrQDR_JYkQF1d9_HY",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "curtain",
      "back": "a piece of hanging cloth that can be pulled across to cover a window, divide a room etc",
      "example": "red velvet curtains"
    },
    {
      "id": "2ooD8XjN4O9HtypquZEsX",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "claustrophobia claus‧tro‧pho‧bi‧a /ˌklɔːstrəˈfəʊbiə",
      "back": "مرض ترس از فضای تنگ ومحصور,a strong fear of being in a small enclosed space or in a situation that limits what you can do",
      "example": "I get claustrophobic in elevators."
    },
    {
      "id": "VSUfTwRI70XF4-ctmZX_x",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "every other week",
      "back": "jede andere Woche, \"Every other week\" is a phrase that indicates that an event or occurrence happens once every two weeks, with a week in between. It is also known as \"bi-weekly\" or \"fortnightly.\"",
      "example": "Sarah's book club meets every other week on Wednesday evenings, giving members enough time to finish the assigned reading and prepare for the discussion."
    },
    {
      "id": "L7fyBuP8t44HI74oF2lt0",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "be accustomed to (doing) something",
      "back": "عادت داشتن به, to be familiar with something and accept it as normal",
      "example": "We were accustomed to working together."
    },
    {
      "id": "TjZ9TzoHJEP06tYO2t4uS",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "what's the difference between be + adjective, e.g., be old, be used to, and get + adjective, e.g., get old, get used to?",
      "back": "\"be + adjective\" and \"get + adjective\" differ in expressing state or condition. The former is static and the latter is changing. For example, \"He is old\" means he has always been old, while \"He is getting old\" means he is becoming old over time.",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "m5Ri8NYkdvtDUbH-44Juy",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "be used to VS get used to?",
      "back": "“Be used to” and “get used to” are phrases that describe familiarity or adaptation to something. “Be used to” means already being familiar with something, while “get used to” means becoming familiar with something.",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "bCcuDtaBfa_0rmjsxCDTF",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "literally",
      "back": "buchstäblich,به معنای واقعی کلمه",
      "example": "She literally ate a whole cake"
    },
    {
      "id": "Ux3oCfeUuamzcybCYB1Fy",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "the use of \"would\" instead of \"used to\"",
      "back": "\"would\" wird normalerweise verwendet, um die Betonung auf die Handlung oder Gewohnheit zu legen, während \"used to\" betont, dass diese Handlung oder Gewohnheit nicht mehr stattfindet.",
      "example": "\"When I was a child, I would play with dolls for hours.\" (statt \"When I was a child, I used to play with dolls for hours.\") \"My grandfather would always tell me stories about his youth.\" (statt \"My grandfather used to always tell me stories about his youth.\") \"She would go for a run every morning before work.\" (statt \"She used to go for a run every morning before work.\") In diesen Beispielen betonen alle Sätze eine wiederholte Handlung in der Vergangenheit, und \"would\" wird anstelle von \"used to\" verwendet, um diese Handlungen auszudrücken."
    },
    {
      "id": "N47ek3CCviCo4TXL8Ek47",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "herb",
      "back": "گیاه دارویی",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "t_lpSZDBsxCb6pnWLyTmE",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "peas",
      "back": "نخود فرنگی",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "dRTyp7ooUP-el6cdrTkgF",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "prize",
      "back": "جایزه",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "wpbem8LNemJIOZHb4DFOF",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "used to (sound)",
      "back": "usta",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "2EKfAZ0nZbLqMCEhDNVBz",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "loose",
      "back": "شل, گشاد",
      "example": "a loose tooth.\nshe slipped into a loose T-shirt and shorts"
    },
    {
      "id": "_esVg1s88E52JCYpNt87S",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "will no doubt be relieved",
      "back": "بدون شک راحت خواهد شد",
      "example": "You will no doubt be relieved to hear that your test results were negative"
    },
    {
      "id": "YKz75mSllxkKISyMJb-v5",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "sew",
      "back": "nähen",
      "example": "She sewed the two sides together."
    },
    {
      "id": "LFUkZehBJDrqLuTvnof1t",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "arguably",
      "back": "شاید، قابل بحث, wohl",
      "example": "Senna was arguably the greatest racing driver of all time."
    },
    {
      "id": "qqIlXyKgC7G8w0T5KMXng",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "long for",
      "back": "to want something very much, especially when it seems unlikely to happen soon",
      "example": "She longed for the chance to speak to him in private."
    },
    {
      "id": "Ypf3tBunMv6DJHzdp3MZp",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "yawn",
      "back": "خمیازه",
      "example": "he began yawning and looking at his watch"
    },
    {
      "id": "YqVB2PiZ43kU6A_pKaOK8",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "comforter",
      "back": "American English a cover for a bed that is filled with a soft warm material such as feathers SYN duvet British English, لحاف",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "wKolTbTt_VsjK8oEzjxya",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "mite",
      "back": "کنه. spoken a small child, especially one that you feel sorry for ",
      "example": "Poor mite! You must be starving!"
    },
    {
      "id": "09V4ojb9LbneDvSxF9ogB",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "sedate  sɪˈdeɪt",
      "back": "to give someone drugs to make them calm or to make them sleep",
      "example": "He was still in shock, and heavily sedated."
    },
    {
      "id": "AV8PUugFjFhiluK2RScFR",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "sleep like a dog",
      "back": "It means to sleep soundly",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "ZxvIfj-peZqJUB5KgrexJ",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "be a light sleeper",
      "back": "means to wake up easily",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "YUPdgJCpw6wFDm4xWXs1M",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "To be fast asleep",
      "back": "to be in a deep sleep",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "OEovNNyd2QipnIPyXSrUs",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "To sleep like a log",
      "back": "to sleep very well, without being woken by any noises",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "I2SjAdUfHJUmYwqDjnCdU",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "steadfast ",
      "back": "ثابت قدم",
      "example": "her father’s steadfast love for her"
    }
  ]
=======
{
  "flashcards": [
    {
      "id": "N5Y1y2kUadl6K8vSIDkom",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "Don't even",
      "back": "\"Don't even\" is a slang expression meaning \"not even\" or \"don't bother.\" It's used to warn someone not to do or say something, expressing surprise, outrage, or rejection.",
      "example": "Person 1: \"Can you lend me some money?\"\nPerson 2: \"Don't even think about it.\""
    },
    {
      "id": "tUqyn5p945dCuLRlizvzp",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "committed",
      "back": "verpflichtet",
      "example": "We are fully committed to Equal Opportunity policies."
    },
    {
      "id": "l0WWhK4q6pnIwqfRDBsmT",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "One or two differences",
      "back": "a lot ... (know a thing or two about something)",
      "example": "She knows a thing or two about international law (Sie weißt viel und ist erfahren)"
    },
    {
      "id": "wzZDlWEMdt8-QG7oPr-w1",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "To be well put toghether",
      "back": "looks good and dresses well (حواسشون به لباس پوشیدنشون هست)",
      "example": "She's elegant and well put toghether."
    },
    {
      "id": "5t38KWgl3bbDk1hDKLtK5",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "acknowledge",
      "back": "anerkennen",
      "example": "Both defendants refused to acknowledge the authority of the court.\nShe won't acknowledge that there's a problem."
    },
    {
      "id": "G1GlZKHcJnWSPUfzFOWgG",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "mean",
      "back": "gemein",
      "example": "That was a mean thing to do."
    },
    {
      "id": "C7wv4SqgtrLnX5nuxQI2e",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "tease",
      "back": "ärgern",
      "example": "She used to tease me about my hair."
    },
    {
      "id": "88V2pR3qQzb4eUFVxZBB8",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "Few nights in to s.th",
      "back": "از اول تا آخر چیزی",
      "example": "The movie was terrible. 30 minutes into it, l left the theater."
    },
    {
      "id": "QgjEFwJuLm-Dt8psn1kJQ",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "To be like",
      "back": "to say",
      "example": "I was like, \"What's the best way to learn English?\""
    },
    {
      "id": "bk7NU6sPJVjCbf59thzJ2",
      "box": 4,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "someone or s.th is somthing else",
      "back": "کسی یا چیزی استسنایی یا خاصه(er ist was anderes)",
      "example": "They're all good soccer players, but Mark is really something else."
    },
    {
      "id": "wn-zQ6WcsBgol2lITVRpU",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "four basic conditional forms?",
      "back": "",
      "example": "1.Zero Conditional: Used to express a general truth or a scientific fact.\nExample: \"If you heat ice, it melts.\"\n\n2.First Conditional: Used to express a future possibility or probability.\nExample: \"If it rains, I will stay at home.\"\n\n3.Second Conditional: Used to express an imaginary or hypothetical situation.\nExample: \"If I won the lottery, I would buy a house.\"\n\n4.Third Conditional: Used to express a hypothetical past situation and its hypothetical past result.\nExample: \"If I had studied harder, I would have passed the exam.\""
    },
    {
      "id": "2ukEDi68fCCXvshkp4QhZ",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "second or third conditionals?",
      "back": "",
      "example": "1) Second Conditional: Describes a hypothetical ***present or future*** situation and its likely outcome.\nIf she had a car, she could drive to work.\nIf I knew how to swim, I would go to the beach more often.\n\n2) Third Conditional: Describes a hypothetical ***past situation*** and its imagined result.\nIf I had gone to the party, I would have met her.\nIf I had studied harder, I would have passed the exam."
    },
    {
      "id": "pGC-qpQXgtWbQsXl8x7p0",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 8,
      "front": "Mixed conditionals?",
      "back": "",
      "example": "Mixed conditionals are a combination of two or more different conditionals (e.g. first, second, third) in one sentence to express a hypothetical situation and its outcome. These types of sentences are used to talk about a situation that started in the past and has consequences in the present or future.\n\nHere are a few examples of mixed conditionals:\n\nIf she had listened to the advice, she wouldn't be in this situation now. (third conditional + second conditional)\nIf I had known about the traffic, I would be at work now. (third conditional + present simple)\nIf he had taken his umbrella, he wouldn't be wet now. (third conditional + present continuous)"
    },
    {
      "id": "f_KXya7icYTuTABXToQQl",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "Umgangsprachliche \"This is going to get you\"",
      "back": "this is gonna getch-ya",
      "example": "\"This is going to get you\" bedeutet in der Regel, dass etwas negative Auswirkungen auf jemanden haben wird oder dass jemand in Schwierigkeiten geraten wird."
    },
    {
      "id": "Ok6pP_rqMVNMT_JzfIUU0",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "out there",
      "back": "anywhere outside",
      "example": "\"There are so many opportunities waiting for us out there, we just need to be brave enough to go after them.\""
    },
    {
      "id": "Tu4foX5gRWQ_kYxzAiao9",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "Umgangssprachliche \"Had you ...\"",
      "back": "ha-ju ....",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "iREP1fy1Wu6l4G4lx1ouc",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "attorney",
      "back": "Rechtsanwalt",
      "example": "\"My attorney advised me to take the plea deal to avoid a lengthy court battle.\""
    },
    {
      "id": "ZjGbN6VlHPi16SywiY5Fy",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "would (andere Bedeutung)",
      "back": "a routine action in the past",
      "example": "When I was a kid my grandma always would tell me to eat all my vegetables."
    },
    {
      "id": "XXvBxXiAqGDFOadz8hRsF",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "Get into trouble",
      "back": "Schwierigkeiten bekommem oder in Schwierigkeiten geraten",
      "example": "he got into trouble with the police."
    },
    {
      "id": "wkWqPQfq-mblbWslDb1U1",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "white picket fence",
      "back": "The american Dream (a strong symbol)",
      "example": "Der Begriff wird oft verwendet, um das Konzept einer perfekten, friedlichen und sicheren Umgebung zu beschreiben"
    },
    {
      "id": "Pw8bYhfIjIwda2ei-GOYc",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "Doing what i'm doing",
      "back": "dass man an seiner gegenwärtigen Arbeit, seinem Projekt oder seiner Verpflichtung festhält und weitermacht.",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "C9QtLoXScG0uLGHfvXvbE",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Good old (ol')",
      "back": "for something reliable (vertraut)",
      "example": "All I need to feel happy is my favorite music and this good ol' journal"
    },
    {
      "id": "jB9rdO5O25zfd9y29xQEB",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "A lot of times (sound?)",
      "back": "a-lodda times",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "X0oqvddu7Yw0DZCNZqTQL",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "Get on well with someone",
      "back": "get along with someone(American)",
      "example": "I get on well with my mother-in-law"
    },
    {
      "id": "1wQJYF2V3p3v7KecINxwv",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "Down-to-earth",
      "back": "bodenständig",
      "example": "Fran’s a friendly, down-to-earth person."
    },
    {
      "id": "Uf385Iysk-SM_KitG2mSv",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "Stick together",
      "back": "if people stick together, they continue to support each other when they have problems (zusammenhalten)",
      "example": "We’re a family, and we stick together no matter what."
    },
    {
      "id": "UrR7BZgtcWSuJkXZK4UJX",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "Hurl",
      "back": "to throw something with a lot of force, especially because you are angry",
      "example": "They hurled a rock through the window"
    },
    {
      "id": "UTNWkSSBsqO95-2j-umPS",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "Plummet",
      "back": "abstürzen",
      "example": "The plane plummeted towards the Earth."
    },
    {
      "id": "L9Hwv-DslYjoI7--aMjQW",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 7,
      "front": "chute (شوت)",
      "back": "short for parachute",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "tYW-8zIFiXbh-tnLSWu-M",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "Eight by ten glossies (گلاسیس) of my life",
      "back": "اون حالتی که قبل مرگ تمام خاطرات جلوی چشم آدم میاد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "16KBwX708F0WZ0y17zQAi",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 6,
      "front": "Why do I have to die today (sound?)",
      "back": "why do i hafta die du-day",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "6ScietzgEOLw0gsvKYEgQ",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "nasal breathing",
      "back": "Nasenatmung",
      "example": "Nasal breathing helps to keep the mouth closed, which can improve overall breathing."
    },
    {
      "id": "p5mnrewVMD7yA3qDxevy3",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "Flossing ",
      "back": "Zahnseide, Zahnseide benutzen",
      "example": "Flossing has several advantages for oral health"
    },
    {
      "id": "bWZvmSC47RdlN-6nTRfYj",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "to come in late ",
      "back": " to arrive at a place after the expected or scheduled time",
      "example": "I'm afraid I'll come in late to the meeting today"
    },
    {
      "id": "v9bK9K44q54zU5lPwht4O",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "Raving about something",
      "back": "to express strong and enthusiastic praise or admiration for something",
      "example": "I was raving about the new restaurant I tried last night"
    },
    {
      "id": "0Ez9Np9pKetON_JPOo9Mv",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "To binge-watch",
      "back": "to watch multiple episodes of a television show or multiple movies in a single sitting, often in one day or over a short period of time.",
      "example": "I've been binge-watching the season since this morning."
    },
    {
      "id": "y4UG1YDCOSwLxX6vm8X6s",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "Ahead of time",
      "back": "means before the scheduled or expected time",
      "example": "I finished my work ahead of time"
    },
    {
      "id": "bUWjIKTGmgqZZUuKWdMje",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "This is going to be huge",
      "back": "it is going to become very popular or famous",
      "example": "I think this band is going to be huge."
    },
    {
      "id": "gPCBukZrbXXqY2RPc_Cmj",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "one of those things",
      "back": " is used to describe something that is difficult to explain or understand, or something that is unpredictable or beyond control",
      "example": "It's just one of those things, there's not much we can do about it"
    },
    {
      "id": "jDL7936KusaRnh7TrUyd_",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "to make it",
      "back": " means to succeed or to achieve something, especially in a difficult or competitive situation",
      "example": "We need to make it to the top of the mountain if we want to see the view"
    },
    {
      "id": "_aO3VAvD2roVyvEyj1d27",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "Duvet",
      "back": "لحاف",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "zn6TKxU6-rb08izTdbhlo",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "sheet",
      "back": "ملافه",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "p1igMoSZ-xifcj9fMcqY2",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "to yank",
      "back": "to pull or tug something suddenly and with force",
      "example": "He yanked her to her feet"
    },
    {
      "id": "RINSjK7FBu6ZfmEHZqofa",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 5,
      "front": "Tasefully done",
      "back": "that something has been done in a way that is pleasing to the senses or in good taste",
      "example": "I usually find tattoss ugly, but i like hers. It is small and tasteful."
    },
    {
      "id": "NDAGAV4ycd0GS_PLRo6bD",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "it drives me crazy wenn...",
      "back": "es macht mich wahnsinnig wenn... دیوانه ام می کند",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "7JoHo7x5HKWcUMJ3P6JPH",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "wish + past simple",
      "back": "is used to express that we want a situation in the present (or future) to be different.",
      "example": "I wish I spoke Italian. (I don’t speak Italian)\nI wish I had a big car. (I don’t have a big car)\nI wish I were on a beach. (I’m in the office)\nI wish it were the weekend. (It’s only Wednesday)"
    },
    {
      "id": "Zz-vjhY1fo9jexdsdvNeb",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "Wish + would / wouldn't",
      "back": "wish + would + bare infinitive is used to express impatience, annoyance or dissatisfaction with a present action.",
      "example": "I wish you would stop smoking.\nYou are smoking at the moment and it is annoying me.\n\nI wish it would stop raining.\nI’m impatient because it is raining and I want to go outside.\n\nI wish she’d be quiet.\nI am annoyed because she is speaking."
    },
    {
      "id": "5mcDcaHADB4rUddcKbQIP",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "wish + past perfect",
      "back": "is used to express a regret, or that we want a situation in the past to be different.",
      "example": "I wish I hadn’t eaten so much. (I ate a lot)\nI wish they’d come on holiday with us. (They didn’t come on holiday)\nI wish I had studied harder at school. (I was lazy at school)"
    },
    {
      "id": "8FcmEmiDolIuHvzYx5uLu",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "if only",
      "back": "used instead of \"i wish\" to express deep regret",
      "example": "If only I had paid more attention in class, I would have understood the material better. (The speaker expresses regret about not paying enough attention in a past class, wishing they had understood the material better.)"
    },
    {
      "id": "btZpfbxrzX5QD-Bl1xI-_",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "blush",
      "back": "erröten,  to become red in the face, usually because you are embarrassed",
      "example": "Wilson saw she was watching him and blushed."
    },
    {
      "id": "_aESdt9nIqbgZ7CARHgEC",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "dumb",
      "back": " informal stupid",
      "example": "What a dumb question."
    },
    {
      "id": "Va0JZ_7WHk03olGcQzrls",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "urge ",
      "back": "a strong wish or need SYN desire",
      "example": "He could no longer resist the urge to go and see Amanda."
    },
    {
      "id": "1pqc-TIpJtjWrMZh9A7st",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "kneel",
      "back": "زانو زدن",
      "example": "Tom knelt down and patted the dog."
    },
    {
      "id": "-E0-6ZYQnBsFCAUTuyU3M",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "Do you get that from people?",
      "back": "Do people tell you that? مردم زیاد بهت میگن؟",
      "example": "A:Man, you really look like Chandler from Friends.\nB: I get that a lot."
    },
    {
      "id": "DuLhKg-uwwBSjLJvP0mh7",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "what's up? meaning and sound?",
      "back": "was geht? (wassup), چه خبر",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "aS9588u4yIIa13ytGqgvo",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "from afar",
      "back": "از دور",
      "example": "I saw him from afar."
    },
    {
      "id": "Aj6VU16WPygxuk98OTawb",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "nuts /nʌts/",
      "back": " informal  crazy",
      "example": "I’m going to go nuts (=become crazy) if I don’t find a new job soon."
    },
    {
      "id": "GztdlSQext74AfS4LAsQB",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "be nuts about/over somebody/something",
      "back": " informal to like someone or something very much",
      "example": "My wife is nuts about kids."
    },
    {
      "id": "Af5K6Lrq5C0tfYSquckXf",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "mud /mʌd/",
      "back": "گل و لای",
      "example": "By the end of the game, all the kids were covered in mud."
    },
    {
      "id": "0gKyp582Jk4-FKK3Vy2lk",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "harrowing ˈhærəʊɪŋ ",
      "back": "very frightening or shocking and making you feel very upset. qualvoll",
      "example": "a harrowing experience"
    },
    {
      "id": "E1_1_aSAvOSh8VToRxVAf",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "warehouse",
      "back": "انبار",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "3kdFGmy7vrHShRtJO5B1R",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "contraption kənˈtræpʃən",
      "back": "a piece of equipment or machinery that looks funny, strange, and unlikely to work well",
      "example": "a bizarre contraption"
    },
    {
      "id": "dBM6W-roAWvOVQMIczh1c",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "go haywire ˈheɪwaɪə ",
      "back": "informal to start working in completely the wrong way",
      "example": "My computer’s gone haywire"
    },
    {
      "id": "WEynDla4oSp-cD6E3l0pn",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "make a point of doing something",
      "back": "bedeutet, dass man sich bewusst Zeit nimmt und Anstrengungen unternimmt, um etwas zu tun, das man für wichtig hält.",
      "example": "I always make a point of being early."
    },
    {
      "id": "PDvThGjF68TPk2kqpdmRR",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "big deal",
      "back": "an important or exciting event or situation",
      "example": "This audition is a big deal for Joey."
    },
    {
      "id": "eqZzDXuk_WH2X1Beg_2Lt",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "no big deal",
      "back": "used to say that you do not think something is as important as someone else thinks it is",
      "example": "It’s no big deal. Everybody forgets things sometimes"
    },
    {
      "id": "dDMEW5N-sOBMcec8_NSO8",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "testicle  ˈtestɪkəl",
      "back": "Hoden, خایه",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "vFqXOpVTEsFxtSNTc6jpb",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "it pains somebody to do something",
      "back": "formal used to say that it is very difficult and upsetting for someone to have to do something",
      "example": "Most burglars, it pains me to say, are just looking for the easy dollar."
    },
    {
      "id": "veNKgk5WVrAjMaTHdLZLr",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "to mess with someone",
      "back": "sich mit jemandem anlegen",
      "example": "I've warned you already, don't mess with me!"
    },
    {
      "id": "EG8EpS8Y0s2xHfpedH4IK",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "endeavor ɪnˈdevə ",
      "back": "formal to try very hard",
      "example": "We always endeavor to please our customers."
    },
    {
      "id": "t7gMK_0480lqPZCzAvOl5",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "voluntarily",
      "back": "freiwillig, به طور داوطلبانه",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "gJqsRsCNW5aNQuoVHj257",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "kind of (sound)",
      "back": "kina کاینا",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "UAEgYzV7FzqIGQYyiPhRL",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "mess up phrasal verb informal",
      "back": "to make a mistake and do something badly",
      "example": "I think I messed up on the last question."
    },
    {
      "id": "S0SvH5UXgBl5N3jkodOmw",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "shot ",
      "back": "informal an attempt to do something or achieve something, especially something difficult",
      "example": "I didn’t think I had much chance of winning the race, but I thought I’d give it a shot (=try to do it)."
    },
    {
      "id": "ZjdHwU1O_cIHAv9Naqjla",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "to blow",
      "back": "informal to lose a good opportunity by making a mistake or by being careless",
      "example": "You’ve got a great future ahead of you. Don’t blow it."
    },
    {
      "id": "W8c4zyQ52qTepjCmM_f1K",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "be meant for somebody",
      "back": "if two people are meant for each other, they are very suitable as partners for each other",
      "example": "They were meant for each other(Sie waren füreinander bestimmt.)."
    },
    {
      "id": "FcVkNYumwf3rcpptOPtQ3",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "mental ˈmentl",
      "back": "British English informal thinking or behaving in a way that seems crazy or strange",
      "example": "He must be mental!(Er muss verrückt sein!)"
    },
    {
      "id": "6qkRZ7CP7tgkEDk6q01ZW",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "wig ",
      "back": "Perücke",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "1NjRnOn2px_72LxSiodVA",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "itchy ˈɪtʃi",
      "back": "خارش‌دار , juckend",
      "example": "My eyes sometimes get red and itchy in the summer."
    },
    {
      "id": "sEg2yNdxkAZm9abtm2pNQ",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "sue",
      "back": "verklagen",
      "example": "If the builders don’t fulfil their side of the contract, we’ll sue."
    },
    {
      "id": "Q8Y-fYinb_Drj9JHSwniN",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "flick through",
      "back": "Durchblättern",
      "example": "Will flicked through Carla’s photo album."
    },
    {
      "id": "4Kr84G0A0qHOl4Ih8FGZi",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "make it",
      "back": " informal to continue to live after you have been seriously ill or badly injured",
      "example": "Frank was very ill, and the doctors didn’t think he’d make it"
    },
    {
      "id": "5jBXXrJdGhzWKzF6o5M1X",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "screw around",
      "back": "informal to do silly things that may cause trouble SYN mess around",
      "example": "The kids were screwing around down by the bus station."
    },
    {
      "id": "d-z5v2PrjI8i3Hls1QCkS",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "culprit  ˈkʌlprɪt",
      "back": "مقصر",
      "example": "Police finally managed to catch the culprit."
    },
    {
      "id": "cY_Lxd1GBUVRw8CA06rvt",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "root for somebody",
      "back": "informal to want someone to succeed in a competition, test, or difficult situation",
      "example": "You can do it – I’m rooting for you"
    },
    {
      "id": "FbdQ8iwLiYhvfSKtqXyWj",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "knackered ˈnækəd ",
      "back": "adjective British English spoken informal  too old or broken to use",
      "example": "a knackered old bike"
    },
    {
      "id": "f1yiuhAJuWCTS1YB0qFCg",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "how did that go?",
      "back": "Wie ging das?  چطور شد؟",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "ykfPRjoBRiiu_dTJPEdmp",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "so that in essence",
      "back": "also im Wesentlichen",
      "example": "I condensed my report to only include the key findings so that in essence, the reader can quickly grasp the main points."
    },
    {
      "id": "1KYctKQytFewXzqCi_FFY",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "on the flip side",
      "back": "bedeutet, dass man eine andere Perspektive oder Sichtweise betrachtet. Es wird verwendet, um einen Gegensatz oder eine Alternative zu einer bereits vorgestellten Idee oder Argumentation darzustellen. ",
      "example": "On the flip side, while the new policy may be beneficial in some ways, it could also result in unintended consequences that need to be considered."
    },
    {
      "id": "A7tEVdZRyi98EuSkrSCjx",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "that is freaking awesome",
      "back": "das ist wahnsinnig toll",
      "example": "The new virtual reality game is so realistic and immersive, that is freaking awesome!"
    },
    {
      "id": "URXAhevH84TBcAbussPX0",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "revert to",
      "back": " zurückzukehren oder zurückzugreifen auf etwas, das man früher hatte oder tat.",
      "example": "Due to technical difficulties, we had to revert to the manual process for the time being until the system is fixed."
    },
    {
      "id": "6jjSi-VWblyLrWMQkZGJK",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "To be tricky",
      "back": "bedeutet, dass jemand schwierig, knifflig oder listig ist. Es kann bedeuten, dass eine Person absichtlich versucht, andere zu täuschen oder zu verwirren.",
      "example": "The crossword puzzle was tricky, but I finally figured out all the answers."
    },
    {
      "id": "t4QfdNcWZDaxNv7lbvhem",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "no fucking way",
      "back": "auf keinen Fall",
      "example": "I heard that the company is planning to lay off half the staff, and I'm telling you, there's no fucking way that's going to happen without a fight"
    },
    {
      "id": "tnkDDD8t8xI2HmP_r5dSx",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "To sleep over",
      "back": "to sleep at another person's house",
      "example": "I slept over at my friend's house."
    },
    {
      "id": "oo0ImP9AtOtI75ncRnDIA",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "no way",
      "back": "a stronger way of saying no",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "p9oYZDnFclJB0AgSVMSGu",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "to go for a wee",
      "back": "is a colloquial expression used to describe someone going to urinate.",
      "example": "he went for a wee."
    },
    {
      "id": "DpRiE2X5KBoUC7WliptYU",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "favorite curse word",
      "back": "Lieblingsschimpfwort",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "hVn3MiITbMU3ANIRfwZWk",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "go out on a limb",
      "back": "The expression is often used to describe a situation where someone takes a bold or unpopular stance, or makes a bold or risky decision.",
      "example": "John decided to go out on a limb and start his own business, even though he knew it would be a big risk."
    },
    {
      "id": "VOicgMd7esVcuC56pPazI",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "What is your (sound)",
      "back": "waddiz-yir ",
      "example": "waddiz-yir favorite body part?"
    },
    {
      "id": "TIkskiYvUPro933YnASC-",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "though",
      "back": "spoken used after adding a fact, opinion, or question which seems surprising after what you have just said, or which makes what you have just said seem less true",
      "example": "Two heart attacks in a year. It hasn’t stopped him smoking, though."
    },
    {
      "id": "QGJMAvhQmVBIfMVuC2Mr4",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "perform a task",
      "back": "انجام یک وظیفه یا کاری",
      "example": "the surgeon performed the operation without complications."
    },
    {
      "id": "kR9FG7UzTMzpu7wFjbBtw",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "to curse",
      "back": "schimpfen",
      "example": "Don't curse in front of the kids!"
    },
    {
      "id": "XIBhmNYkiZlxU527de96S",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "impersonate",
      "back": "imitieren,  to pretend to be someone else by copying their appearance, voice, and behaviour, especially in order to deceive people",
      "example": "Do you know it is a very serious offence to impersonate a police officer?"
    },
    {
      "id": "oFmnbqCB9MmJMcPulIohu",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "Yell at",
      "back": "فریاد زدن برسر, Anschreien",
      "example": "He yelled \"Watch out!\""
    },
    {
      "id": "JQkJuQpZ3KPyF5CCPie-t",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "cool-headed",
      "back": "not easily excited or upset, خونسرد",
      "example": "We need a quick-thinking, cool-headed person for the job."
    },
    {
      "id": "AsmEL_FGopmR1G9JqfBZn",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "hothead",
      "back": "someone who does things too quickly without thinking",
      "example": "neither of you hotheads would listen to me when I asked you to stop this nonsense"
    },
    {
      "id": "gC-acuU0Zhj_Wkd0pX56P",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "call somebody/something ↔ off",
      "back": "to decide that a planned event will not take place SYN cancel",
      "example": "The trip to Italy might be called off."
    },
    {
      "id": "IRS_jVzBMPAh2ECKo_rZV",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "go astray",
      "back": "to be lost or stolen",
      "example": "The letter had gone astray in the post."
    },
    {
      "id": "5qXrBR6CDwIbVgyeu5FSp",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "airship",
      "back": "بالون",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "tRI1-176mYnNpUwwZ-6R0",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "debris  ˈdebriː",
      "back": "باقی مانده, خرده",
      "example": "the bomb hits it, showering debris from all sides"
    },
    {
      "id": "ABSbyrAGZxTiRBYLRYhnB",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "fray",
      "back": "increasingly upset or annoying",
      "example": "amid fraying tensions"
    },
    {
      "id": "wFtnfIejRyUzRnkhj1Noj",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "violate  ˈvaɪəleɪt",
      "back": "verletzen, نقض کردن",
      "example": "regimes that violate human rights"
    },
    {
      "id": "xwDdX04vCihEu0aD3eABX",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "territory",
      "back": "Staatsgebiet",
      "example": "The plane was flying over enemy territory."
    },
    {
      "id": "euUNY5faUTDONUXcClsdS",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "sovereign country",
      "back": "کشور مستقل",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "RyLUT2jReWCREzhQZxE1e",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "in a calm and reliable manner",
      "back": "به شیوه ای آرام و قابل اعتماد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "GNKMZ_fXPWLmjdJ03Z8Aq",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "would not accept any groundless conjecture or hype",
      "back": "هیچ گونه حدس و گمان یا هیاهوی بی اساس را نمی پذیرد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "9zUpPJsdvkciOiNH096Zn",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "as a pretext to attack and smear China",
      "back": "بهانه ای برای حمله و لکه دار کردن چین است",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "7xU9toIib5Xh30s_CpVuP",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "US officials",
      "back": "مقامات آمریکایی",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "gwdv2hm7PcR2cMsvpw4Fd",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "missile",
      "back": "موشک",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "0k-fw1oHZ77Dtd_WWItlw",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "the eve of",
      "back": "the night before",
      "example": "I'm planning a nice dinner the eve of my wedding. "
    },
    {
      "id": "kJPEEZfGECpU-GmJDd1an",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "to show up",
      "back": "to arrive",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "K8Ww8LtyzBd3iP_EgBlBT",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "stuck",
      "back": "informal unable to do any more of something that you are working on because it is too difficult",
      "example": "Can you help me with my homework, Dad? I’m stuck."
    },
    {
      "id": "SUa0v1fD33WchMt9hGvDN",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "anticipate   /ænˈtɪsəpeɪt/",
      "back": " to think about something that is going to happen, especially something pleasant SYN look forward to (erwarten)",
      "example": "Daniel was eagerly anticipating her arrival."
    },
    {
      "id": "M-kbntGRtZIFoGgG8NlWL",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "make it to some place",
      "back": "arrive",
      "example": "I can't believe I made it to the job interview in time. I was stuck in traffic for 20 minutes."
    },
    {
      "id": "gO9DXXka4FQOh66CvkC-s",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "tie تای",
      "back": "مساوی ",
      "example": "Who won the game?\nNobody. It was a tie (game/match)."
    },
    {
      "id": "5uDOruGua_rWwwMZZfAfA",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "opt for / opt to do something",
      "back": "to choose one thing or do one thing instead of another, انتخاب کردن",
      "example": "Many young people are opting to go on to college."
    },
    {
      "id": "XS3PpytrDNWNJy0L3IYKX",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "My hair is down",
      "back": "Meine Haare sind offen",
      "example": "opp: My hair is up"
    },
    {
      "id": "mB7VUOxs2dvbTfFwRr3cg",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "wonky /ˈwɒŋki",
      "back": "wackelig",
      "example": "i was wonky"
    },
    {
      "id": "Lcr2heuG3V9oBU8keS9B-",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": " out of sorts",
      "back": "feeling a little ill or upset ",
      "example": "I felt out of sorts after riding in the boat."
    },
    {
      "id": "WrKXRuTXk2cmpQnhMVCcE",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "tummy",
      "back": "Magen",
      "example": "He was up all night with tummy ache."
    },
    {
      "id": "f8DXSU17TXf5hpyNCFUvs",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "for real",
      "back": "wirklich, seriously, not just pretending",
      "example": "After two trial runs we did it for real."
    },
    {
      "id": "PADuK4hYKcSVdJMiBQdoa",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "with my luck...",
      "back": "Pech!, Wie immer!, spoken used to say that you are not surprised something bad has happened to you, because you are usually unlucky",
      "example": "With my luck, gambling is a really bad idea."
    },
    {
      "id": "okXaxFsEeST3H418f4rAM",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "bottoms up!",
      "back": "spoken used to tell someone to enjoy or finish their alcoholic drink",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "VfCSwLyM8Y0_PPDjUEkeJ",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "smooth sailing",
      "back": "happening or operating successfully, without any problems",
      "example": "Sarah is responsible for the smooth sailing of the sales department."
    },
    {
      "id": "X2AYoccU5nrgLTY-tcX39",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "Bottoms up (sound?)",
      "back": "ba-dum-zup  بدمز آپ",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "ZIHrrEGjHGxY5i2HJ9ijI",
      "box": 3,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "sort of thing",
      "back": "Dass etwas typisch ist",
      "example": "Eating peanuts is a very baseball game sort of thing."
    },
    {
      "id": "_uExncVT9bn_SlOx04_f4",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "he hit on me",
      "back": "\"Er hat versucht, mich anzumachen\". Das bedeutet, dass jemand versucht hat, romantische oder sexuelle Aufmerksamkeit von Ihnen zu bekommen.",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "EE61JTtBwFlsazqBS8wdz",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Break down",
      "back": "Zusammenbrechen, fehlschlagen, ausfallen",
      "example": "The car broke down on the highway."
    },
    {
      "id": "48ZxwKKxCwG42eOSuReF5",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Call off",
      "back": "Absagen, abbrechen",
      "example": "We had to call off the party due to bad weather."
    },
    {
      "id": "dwQwvtBQ6-HEX9D0sB4GL",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Come up with",
      "back": "Etwas erfinden, sich etwas ausdenken",
      "example": "I need to come up with a good excuse for being late."
    },
    {
      "id": "NoaXJ6W0-2TlZn2zjpap1",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "Put off",
      "back": "Verschieben, aufschieben",
      "example": "I keep putting off doing my taxes."
    },
    {
      "id": "tf5m0FOCX1odGipKFTKrf",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "Turn down",
      "back": "Ablehnen, abweisen",
      "example": "I applied for the job, but they turned me down."
    },
    {
      "id": "qgC5781pbSo6n1ww8gbDT",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 4,
      "front": "Work out",
      "back": "Sich herausstellen, funktionieren, trainieren",
      "example": "I hope everything works out in the end."
    },
    {
      "id": "pHC8GId428Jrt-xgr8SGT",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "Bring up",
      "back": "Jemanden auf etwas ansprechen, aufziehen (Kinder)",
      "example": "I don't want to bring up that topic again."
    },
    {
      "id": "2DwkGmMpvIz3JLhaVelE_",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "Put up with",
      "back": " Etwas ertragen, sich mit etwas abfinden",
      "example": "I can't put up with his behavior anymore."
    },
    {
      "id": "2FXfgqt1xfW2KXaDgDkVQ",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "Turn up",
      "back": "Auftauchen, erscheinen, erhöhen",
      "example": "He turned up at the party unexpectedly."
    },
    {
      "id": "GtMxMSnj-D9y9XKCLXTSX",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "Get away",
      "back": "Wegkommen, fliehen, eine Pause machen",
      "example": "I need to get away from work for a few days."
    },
    {
      "id": "j9Tw5zLmK1rN8sQ2fYxuq",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "procrastinate",
      "back": "aufschieben",
      "example": "I tend to procrastinate when I have a lot of work to do."
    },
    {
      "id": "s7Tk2hPnL8qF3mJ6dYxrz",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "reliable",
      "back": "zuverlässig",
      "example": "He is a reliable worker who always gets the job done on time."
    },
    {
      "id": "t9X2f8kYj1rL7sG6mDxuq",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "vulnerable",
      "back": "verletzlich",
      "example": "She felt vulnerable after the breakup."
    },
    {
      "id": "f9T2z1hKj1eL7sG6mDxuq",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "resilient",
      "back": "widerstandsfähig",
      "example": "She is a resilient person who can handle tough situations."
    },
    {
      "id": "g9T2z1hKj1rL7sD6mYxuq",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "spontaneous",
      "back": "spontan",
      "example": "She is a spontaneous person who likes to try new things."
    },
    {
      "id": "p5Ty2fKJh9eL7sG6mDxuq",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "impartial",
      "back": "unparteiisch",
      "example": "The judge was impartial in the case."
    },
    {
      "id": "l5Ty2pLJd1qN8sD6fYxrz",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 3,
      "front": "precise",
      "back": "präzise",
      "example": "He is very precise in his work."
    },
    {
      "id": "y9T2z1hKj1eL7sG6mDxuq",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "versatile",
      "back": "vielseitig",
      "example": "She is a versatile performer who can sing, dance, and act."
    },
    {
      "id": "a5Ty2pLJd1qN8sQ6fYxrz",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "conscientious",
      "back": "gewissenhaft",
      "example": "She is a conscientious worker who always pays attention to details."
    },
    {
      "id": "2udHLlU0SIazVUwrk6XyA",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "Clunky and verbose",
      "back": "bedeutet, dass etwas schwerfällig und umständlich ist und dabei unnötig viele Worte verwendet werden.",
      "example": "The program's documentation was clunky and verbose, spanning hundreds of pages even though most of the information could have been summarized in just a few."
    },
    {
      "id": "x9CdOfnLs-moT2ho-bt6L",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "schema",
      "back": "طرح , das Schema, die Darstellung",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "dvqcHPoasy3I2ZNGE5Zix",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "for the sake of this tutorial",
      "back": "به خاطر این آموزش",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "TgzYEp2Y_nfEX0qpR76mP",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "you're bound to get replaced",
      "back": "شما باید جایگزین شوید",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "UrQQlHGl3VQEKzg-e7Jkb",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "in response to",
      "back": "als Antwort auf",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "bIP-yYLHc6xDNcO95juJM",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "blog snippet",
      "back": "قطعه وبلاگ, Blogausschnitt",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "ttj1VR5p_ZrlWU-VzwCjO",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "in the face of something",
      "back": "angesichts von etwas, با وجود ",
      "example": "In the face of adversity, she remained steadfast and focused on her goals."
    },
    {
      "id": "hQ7jx7SHEDGuzZXcqMUBo",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "to be eligible",
      "back": "anspruchsberechtigt sein, berechtigt sein zu, واجد شرایط بودن",
      "example": "In order to be eligible for the scholarship, applicants must have a minimum GPA of 3.5."
    },
    {
      "id": "1EnC0Z-g0zb0PRq1LTIL1",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "infuriate  ɪnˈfjʊərieɪt ",
      "back": "to make someone extremely angry SYN anger",
      "example": "It infuriated him that Beth was with another man."
    },
    {
      "id": "nfoyrMvzMg8OLfU8XPFEB",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "offensive   əˈfensɪv",
      "back": "very rude or insulting and likely to upset people OPP inoffensive",
      "example": "I found her remarks deeply offensive."
    },
    {
      "id": "PkwQpOtHHTNGhbcaRn2ui",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "freshman year dorm room",
      "back": "اتاق خواب سال اول, Studentenwohnheim im ersten Jahr",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "zWZXnQ7LJKuNVHTWGpYgj",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "devastatingly",
      "back": " to an extremely impressive degree.",
      "example": "a devastatingly attractive man"
    },
    {
      "id": "QXVmjD4M18TXk0WBiC-KX",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "sorrow  ˈsɒrəʊ ",
      "back": "Kummer, Leid , غم و اندوه",
      "example": "He expressed his sorrow at my father’s death."
    },
    {
      "id": "o7B9HHs8dV_s5tcdbGS5E",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "encouraging",
      "back": "viel versprechend, دلگرم کننده",
      "example": "The signs are encouraging — but there’s a long way to go."
    },
    {
      "id": "sdgnNBsQeUHvS48XO68Q6",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "alongside",
      "back": "در کنار",
      "example": "Children’s prices are shown alongside adult prices."
    },
    {
      "id": "FmyVWDK9PhBT80eZT9m6v",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "intriguing     ɪnˈtriːɡɪŋ",
      "back": "جذاب , faszinierend",
      "example": "The magazine carries an intriguing mixture of high fashion, gossip and racing."
    },
    {
      "id": "MMBuRhVhMvWZzPa_P9t8X",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "brave",
      "back": "شجاع",
      "example": "a brave soldier"
    },
    {
      "id": "vcIS1J6LsIuHL08CyVQeG",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "I'm absolutely sure we would have gotten along",
      "back": "من کاملا مطمئن هستم که با هم کنار می آمدیم",
      "example": "Ich bin mir absolut sicher, dass wir uns verstanden hätten"
    },
    {
      "id": "49ACGOvLy7lHcpxYW6z8v",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "eager  ˈiːɡə ",
      "back": "very keen and excited about something that is going to happen or about something you want to do, مشتاق",
      "example": "I was eager to get back to work as soon as possible."
    },
    {
      "id": "wBfDPZpKaS5LQBcWPbPLw",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "eager to please",
      "back": "eifrig zu gefallen,  مشتاق خوشحال کردن دیگران",
      "example": "She’s a very hard worker and very eager to please."
    },
    {
      "id": "HAyMZT-y-vjvLiUayKh3T",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 2,
      "front": " every now and then/again",
      "back": "(also every so often) sometimes, but not often or regularly. hin und wieder, هرازگاهی/دوباره",
      "example": "I still see her every now and then."
    },
    {
      "id": "Z9pfdRmSgC_9TAgm0DUbd",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "if it's of any help",
      "back": "falls es was hilft, اگر کمکی باشد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "_gvIGfolxPkDZWp3b5dBc",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "One hell of a high five",
      "back": "",
      "example": "dass die gegebene High Five (Hand abklatschen) besonders beeindruckend oder außergewöhnlich gut war. Es kann verwendet werden, um jemanden für eine besonders gute Leistung oder eine großartige Leistung zu loben."
    },
    {
      "id": "AueKSeOtiwq2BrsMvfj-x",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "foreshadow  fɔːˈʃædəʊ ",
      "back": "to show or say that something will happen in the future, vorausahnen lassen,پیش بینی ",
      "example": "The revolution foreshadowed an entirely new social order."
    },
    {
      "id": "2rpikmo9nVSavJQeFUp-H",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "wink",
      "back": "چشمک",
      "example": "he winked at Nicole as he passed"
    },
    {
      "id": "VDkeGsdBx42ImEcz2LMUs",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": " spot-on",
      "back": "informal exactly right",
      "example": "Judith is always spot-on with her advice."
    },
    {
      "id": "A4krYJapYecUb3p4ShjJ4",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "To be off",
      "back": "not be close to right.",
      "example": "How far off have they been?"
    },
    {
      "id": "shFhsxz21Vw0O6v94tipH",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "I would have loved to (sound)",
      "back": "I would-a loved to",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "RLU_iqZrvKJuMh22kjN4a",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "let somebody/something ↔ down",
      "back": "to not do something that someone trusts or expects you to do. کسی را ناامید کن",
      "example": "The worst feeling is having let our fans down."
    },
    {
      "id": "ThTxA6RNKR1kSHvWKR_F2",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "butcher",
      "back": " informal to spoil something by working carelessly",
      "example": "That hairdresser really butchered my hair!"
    },
    {
      "id": "wRb8Orn3a5YdxLVtIOiE8",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "You're putting me on the spot",
      "back": "bedeutet, dass man unter Druck gesetzt wird, eine schnelle Entscheidung oder Antwort auf eine Frage oder Situation zu geben, für die man nicht ausreichend vorbereitet ist oder keine klare Antwort hat. Es kann auch bedeuten, dass man sich unwohl oder unsicher fühlt, wenn man in dieser Weise herausgefordert wird.",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "OlU7qC-I268hsJugrScSV",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "rummage  ˈrʌmɪdʒ",
      "back": "(also rummage around/about) to search for something by moving things around in a careless or hurried way. زیر و رو کردن",
      "example": "Looks like someone’s been rummaging around in my desk."
    },
    {
      "id": "adMyYjqhXUmj4g_HJynvC",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "Dumpster  ˈdʌmpstə ",
      "back": "Müllcontainer",
      "example": "There was a Dumpster on the street."
    },
    {
      "id": "W0z99YF6FxNFOHLCVnGfu",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "a whole lot",
      "back": "eine ganze Menge. viel",
      "example": "We’re going to have a whole lot of problems if we don’t finish this by tomorrow."
    },
    {
      "id": "PK3r-5z8d8LEqkgGdk1E7",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "you've got an issue (sound)",
      "back": "you've gah-din issue",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "siBPq0OHeOMAHf1pxev9E",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "intimacy",
      "back": "رابطه نامشروع جنسی. formal sex – used especially by lawyers and police when they want to avoid using the word ‘sex’",
      "example": "Intimacy took place on several occasions."
    },
    {
      "id": "LIfrtYNBUz1iznkDgTuQO",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "To put somebody on blast",
      "back": "",
      "example": "bedeutet, jemanden öffentlich zu kritisieren oder bloßzustellen, oft durch die Verbreitung von Informationen oder Meinungen über diese Person in der Öffentlichkeit oder auf sozialen Medien. Es kann auch bedeuten, jemanden öffentlich zu beschuldigen oder anzugreifen. Der Ausdruck wird oft im Zusammenhang mit einer heftigen Kritik oder einer Kontroverse verwendet."
    },
    {
      "id": "rMo2R5hsgKpMCCvtAepEd",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "to hold on to somebody",
      "back": "if someone holds on to you, they remain with you or they accompany you through a difficult time.",
      "example": "If a memory holds to you, you never forget it. "
    },
    {
      "id": "-Ds_0sKbS6h6AtrL-1eD0",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "supervisor",
      "back": "سرپرست",
      "example": "Any holidays not already booked should be cleared with your supervisor."
    },
    {
      "id": "RXIBuVHVSpMmk6laW5Peu",
      "box": 2,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "occasion",
      "back": "Gelegenheit, مناسبت",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "yq0hAhcHv6HxtNV6VbUjr",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "controversial",
      "back": "بحث برانگیز",
      "example": "Why is the Koh-i-Noor diamond so controversial?"
    },
    {
      "id": "MBkd8WDhDog6Id1hixEuH",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "that wasn't a good move on your part",
      "back": "این حرکت خوبی از طرف شما نبود",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "I5P3lBwut0BFYGjmXnWMN",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "verse",
      "back": "شعر",
      "example": "Let’s sing the last verse again"
    },
    {
      "id": "JZN4ZosbTm7gVQZ3Zykrz",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "committed environmentalist",
      "back": "engagierter Umweltschützer",
      "example": "محیط بان متعهد"
    },
    {
      "id": "5rO0asqvX9l4vZUSfnOjP",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "ingest  ɪnˈdʒest",
      "back": "aufnehmen, sich nehmen, بلعیدن",
      "example": "lead will poison anyone if enough is ingested"
    },
    {
      "id": "a0JDpCjvs744B0a778IIJ",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "strangely/oddly/curiously etc enough",
      "back": "merkwürdigerweise, used to say that a fact or something that happens is strange or surprising",
      "example": "Strangely enough, I didn’t feel at all nervous when I faced the audience"
    },
    {
      "id": "ot2jW8NQ993pfY_t8wBs8",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "ancient",
      "back": "باستانی کهن",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "84jnRXcWAX0nDUWiynCVA",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "formerly",
      "back": "früher, in earlier times SYN previously",
      "example": "This elegant hotel was formerly a castle."
    },
    {
      "id": "BAvxgtKpwQMmTKQAw3F-W",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": " I think it has got hope",
      "back": "Ich denke, es hat Hoffnung gemacht",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "5PlK79wIvTs4FsHEnv-hb",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "reluctant to do something  rɪˈlʌktənt",
      "back": "unwillig, بی میل بودن",
      "example": "Maddox was reluctant to talk about it."
    },
    {
      "id": "rD7V7uyO0Runo7UJbxSON",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "fragment",
      "back": " قطعه قطعه کردن یا شدن",
      "example": "his followers fragmented into sects"
    },
    {
      "id": "oFYPkli478IeKhEMPeAj3",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "deliberately  dɪˈlɪbərətli",
      "back": "done in a way that is intended or planned به عمد",
      "example": "He deliberately upset her."
    },
    {
      "id": "78U-UrdZr7q_I8LKEvqzi",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "let/get somebody off the hook",
      "back": "was bedeutet, dass jemand von einer Verpflichtung oder Verantwortung befreit wird. to allow someone or help someone to get out of a difficult situation",
      "example": "I wasn’t prepared to let her off the hook that easily."
    },
    {
      "id": "HY6zu07M07gCP4WVVbMeE",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "multifaceted",
      "back": "چند وجهی",
      "example": "a multifaceted campaign to reduce teen pregnancy"
    },
    {
      "id": "JChxHldgNdMtrokK0LpB1",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "thrifty  ˈθrɪfti",
      "back": "using money carefully and wisely SYN economical  sparsam",
      "example": "hard-working, thrifty people"
    },
    {
      "id": "aUHH0UBuZSUsoqBZ4fEwG",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "instil confidence/fear/discipline etc into somebody",
      "back": "to teach someone to think, behave, or feel in a particular way over a period of time.  beibringen, einprägen",
      "example": "A manager’s job is to instil determination into his players"
    },
    {
      "id": "siUFKCbrdquMW65BnjMxL",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "take pride in your work/appearance etc",
      "back": "to do something very carefully and well, in a way that gives you a lot of satisfaction",
      "example": "She took great pride in her appearance.\nYou should take more pride in your work."
    },
    {
      "id": "rp5gBiK0T-Mqs2qx_s1Nt",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "perpetual  pəˈpetʃuəl ",
      "back": "continuing all the time without changing or stopping SYN continuous  ständig",
      "example": "the perpetual noise of the machines"
    },
    {
      "id": "Opx1aefTSNLxKYir9f3yS",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "bins",
      "back": "سطل زباله Mülleimer",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "B87Rzid1qOMObjZpC467M",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "underway",
      "back": "در حال انجام",
      "example": "The project is already well underway."
    },
    {
      "id": "NWDDwZ7tvjRj5-rwGrN7d",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "vaguely",
      "back": "به طور مبهم",
      "example": "he vaguely remembered talking to her once"
    },
    {
      "id": "-j447SJP7sUFTBaM55661",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "get to like/know/understand somebody/something",
      "back": "to gradually begin to like, know, or understand someone or something",
      "example": "It’ll take a while for you to get to know everyone.\nAfter a while, I got to like him."
    },
    {
      "id": "9hbxEwXKYThXo0srIC4b9",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "it makes an impression on you",
      "back": "es macht einen eindruck auf dich, روی شما تاثیر می گذارد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "odzBbQCHzNT2o0R-IWQKq",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 1,
      "front": "Glorified",
      "back": "oft verwendet wird, um eine Person, Sache oder Tätigkeit als überbewertet, aufgebauscht oder übertrieben positiv dargestellt zu beschreiben. تمجید شده ",
      "example": "I did the paperwork and was basically a glorified secretary"
    },
    {
      "id": "feoaWVb0K9I-7k2f15AIw",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "chicken out",
      "back": "informal to decide at the last moment not to do something you said you would do, because you are afraid, ",
      "example": "You’re not chickening out, are you?"
    },
    {
      "id": "pnrBwTl2p5FcjNItOaV5c",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "because he chickened out (sound)",
      "back": "cuz-ee chicken-dout",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "Le8YtXIInIu4Vu-83Hzi7",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "pile",
      "back": "Haufen",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "-cTZoqUZuETaqhqDD-umT",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "gross",
      "back": "spoken very unpleasant to look at or think about SYN disgusting",
      "example": "Ooh, gross! I hate spinach!"
    },
    {
      "id": "Cg4rt44GivE2uFr1sHbIc",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "inside of the forearm",
      "back": "داخل ساعد",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "P6qRar_nq1MebrlLV-OHQ",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "Get out of here!",
      "back": "express disbelief or surprise",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "uABmmivhC4iUImrJcm2C3",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "snap",
      "back": "an exclamation of surprise",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "XMRSFnal1YfoyyL0dDGwc",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "that looks bananas",
      "back": "that is very silly or crazy",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "oTyL6RWb1-IbD9zLxLoj5",
      "box": 1,
      "level": 2,
      "front": "deprecate",
      "back": "Der Begriff deprecate bedeutet, dass etwas veraltet, nicht empfohlen oder abgelehnt ist. Zum Beispiel kann eine Funktion in einem Programm als deprecated markiert werden, wenn sie durch eine neuere oder bessere Funktion ersetzt wird",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "3bMlQqX28aRXCa4bCFclU",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Creep",
      "back": "to move in a quiet, careful way, especially to avoid attracting attention, خزیدن",
      "example": "Johann would creep into the gallery to listen to the singers."
    },
    {
      "id": "6DGKiCL0mYLH7ExyJd1mQ",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Stay grounded",
      "back": "Insgesamt ermutigt \"Stay grounded\" dazu, eine Balance zwischen Ehrgeiz und Realitätssinn zu finden und sich auf das Wesentliche zu konzentrieren, um erfolgreich und glücklich zu sein.",
      "example": "How to Become Disciplined & Stay Grounded"
    },
    {
      "id": "xwfH9K_zDfCs9j47vMzZD",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "resting face",
      "back": "Gesichtsausdruck ",
      "example": "Resting face\" auch als \"Resting Bitch Face\" (kurz RBF) bezeichnet werden, was einen Gesichtsausdruck beschreibt, der unfreundlich oder abweisend wirken kann, auch wenn die Person keine negative Absicht hat."
    },
    {
      "id": "Po3kftn_oIwnxS-RJcoxe",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "forehead",
      "back": "پیشانی",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "ILI8shn6v8hl_BQ4_coKl",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "mole",
      "back": "خال",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "vD6GZTcjUpDQLuZyP7J83",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "to cover something up",
      "back": "پوشاندن چیزی",
      "example": "The company tried to cover up the environmental damage caused by its operations by withholding information from the public and manipulating scientific studies."
    },
    {
      "id": "mtkeRVfjfb3eZ78AW5V43",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "have chemistry",
      "back": "Ausdruck, der oft verwendet wird, um eine starke emotionale oder physische Anziehungskraft zwischen zwei Personen zu beschreiben.",
      "example": "From the moment they met, there was an undeniable chemistry between them that kept them talking and laughing for hours."
    },
    {
      "id": "RTUeQrZHE399sHnyhOPqr",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "The Walk of Fame",
      "back": " ist ein berühmter Gehweg auf dem Hollywood",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "P1pJuqHM31TJZHKf9FXRW",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "beyond the realm of possibility",
      "back": "der bedeutet, dass etwas so unwahrscheinlich oder unrealistisch ist, dass es nicht einmal in Betracht gezogen werden kann.",
      "example": "It's beyond the realm of possibility that we'll be able to travel back in time and change the course of history."
    },
    {
      "id": "w8ONZiu_M-fQSXJUj8zk2",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "badass",
      "back": "that's pretty cool",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "nu1Wi01IsIFyaA8MA_huj",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "wimping out",
      "back": "der bedeutet, vor einer Herausforderung oder einer Verantwortung zurückzuschrecken und nicht mutig oder entschlossen zu handeln.",
      "example": "Instead of wimping out when faced with the challenges of starting a new business, he persevered through difficult times and eventually built a successful company."
    },
    {
      "id": "tD8nLM0jPgkUqRZQ8ZxiC",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "disarming",
      "back": "making you feel less angry or disapproving towards someone, and more friendly",
      "example": "a disarming sense of humor"
    },
    {
      "id": "hD_exEXhdSnukPRbHlytv",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "be/have a blast",
      "back": "it's extremely fun",
      "example": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "c5FpkbV9FXDONJss8hLuD",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "take delight in (doing) something",
      "back": "to enjoy something very much, especially something you should not do",
      "example": "Chris takes great delight in teasing his sister."
    },
    {
      "id": "pByIVQ1oR8W3YlRpN_qg1",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "rub something ↔ in  phrasal verb informal",
      "back": "to remind someone about something they want to forget, especially because they are embarrassed about it",
      "example": "Was he trying to rub in the fact that he didn’t think much of me?"
    },
    {
      "id": "Fej13TE6y99dLcF1VpmyE",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "revelation",
      "back": "Enthüllung. a surprising fact about someone or something that was previously secret and is now made known",
      "example": "He resigned after revelations about his affair"
    },
    {
      "id": "Q3qtFXh4FQuNC7newDp5V",
      "box": 0,
      "level": 0,
      "front": "intrinsically ",
      "back": "ذاتا",
      "example": "Science is seen as intrinsically good."
    }
  ]
>>>>>>> a2d7df8 (Added new vocabularies)
}